Hello.
Hello everyone.
Oh my god, it's been forever.
I'm so happy to be here. Yay.
Yippee.
I hope you guys have been doing good.
Yeah,
you sound great. Thank you. I was
recording
and I didn't even finish recording.
But it's okay cuz I'm going to finish it
after this stream and then tomorrow.
No, I'm not going to push it. No, I'm
going to finish it today.
Yeah. I was so productive, guys.
Yeah.
What have you guys been up to? Hasn't
been that long. I mean, I was streaming.
I I I stream
last weekish.
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, draw. Sleepy.
Draw. Sleepy. Draw.
Oh, you got new glasses. That's nice.
Ooh,
I forgot how your voice sounds like.
That's You're just absurd. There is no
way.
Yeah,
at least this week. If I finish it
today, it'll be so good.
Pulled a $200 out of a booster pack. Oh
my god, that's so that's so awesome.
Whoa. Whoa. That's crazy.
Been stuck studying. Oh, mood.
Wow. Everyone's everyone's been getting
so busy. That's crazy.
Wow.
Bought a condo. That's insane. That's
actually a really big accomplishment.
Oh, it's your birthday. Have fun with
that.
Hope you have a great one, Spacey. Yay.
Yay.
Yeah, it's it's been kind of I don't
know what I've been doing, but every day
I just wake up, I record. I wake up, I
record. I wake up, I record.
And I had to just make sure that I was
on top of things and trying to lock in
as much as possible.
Cuz if I didn't lock in, I was going to
get into a big big trouble and that
would have been really bad.
Oh, it was your birthday yesterday. Oh,
hey. Oh my god. Hope you had a great
one. Nine breaker.
Yay.
Where's the metal pipe? Oh, I muted it.
Oh, you guys you guys missed the metal
pipe, too.
A
that's so that's so sweet of you.
Voice sounds soft today. That's because
I was recording.
And what you can you can tell you can
usually tell when I've been recording
cuz my voice is usually on the lighter
side.
Yeah.
It's a It's a part of streaming now.
Yeah. Oh, if you don't if you don't hear
any pipe sounds, then that's uh that
probably means that it's not crony.
It sounds sweet, but hope your voice is
okay. It's okay. I uh
just got to make sure that I record it
decently.
And you know, honestly, I think
like while I've been recording, I was
going through a little development arc
and I think I made like a pretty big
breakthroughish.
Yeah. Is not by a lot. Maybe a lot, but
it was pretty good.
Yeah. was recording so much that I got a
development arc. It was awesome.
Yeah.
So, just kind of looking forward to
that.
Mhm.
Songs or voice packs? Well,
um
I think a bit of both. Yeah.
I've just been um
well, I haven't been recording voice
packs because I was on top of that.
So, nothing nothing coming in yet, but I
was just recording other things.
Yeah.
I mean, if it was for voice acting, I
would have finished my work a lot
faster, but Yeah.
No Max Hollow voice pack yet. No, not
yet.
Always like there's a voice pack just
around the corner. Yeah, I mean that's
probably because it's already done or
something.
Yeah.
And then and then I' I've lost I've lost
a bit of um weight cuz I've been really
watching myself and I I'm at my lowest.
I'm really happy. I'm at the lowest
weight that I've ever been. I'm really
taking care of myself.
Did you go to the gym? No. Because if I
went to the gym, then I would have been
in
big trouble. I had to hand it in as soon
as possible.
Yeah.
And then and then yesterday I was
Oh, I I procrastinated a bit cuz But
then, you know, it was a while since I
spent time with my family, so I just
spent time with them all day. I was just
looking at the weather. I was thinking,
"Wow, what a what a what a nice
weather."
Yeah.
Oh, beautiful. Birds are singing.
It's very, very chill. It's truly
summer.
Did you celebrate Father's Day with
time, Dad? Um, kind of. We were going to
have like a early father's day dinner
because it was all going to be booked
for Father's Day, right? So, we booked a
nice place and we were going to eat and
then a very important work came up for
him and so
he left
and we just ate by ourselves. Um,
yeah, that was a bit awkward and sad
cuz it was a pretty nice place and we
were just like eating and going and and
right after he left the food started
coming out and we just kind of stared at
the food and was going, "Oh, yeah, that
looks that looks really nice." Um,
yeah, except
the
the main guest isn't here.
Did you pack it for him? Um, yeah, I
think I think we did. Yeah.
But then while we're just eating,
uh, we tried to just try to
I don't know, we tried to make things a
bit lighthearted. And then an extra food
would come out and we'd think, "Oh yeah,
we'd be reminded again that he's not
here." And
yeah, we tried to make the most of it.
Edit him in the photo.
Yeah,
that that was that was something.
Yeah. And then yesterday I was just kind
of having a having a time, chill time.
And then
and then I tagged along uh because
something came up
uh something about the bears
and yeah, I just had to take care of the
bears
um cuz they're causing problems.
Yeah,
bears.
Oh, yeah.
Oh,
oh, there there are bears. Yeah.
Sometimes you can see them walking
around in the school grounds or
in the gas station.
Yeah,
but sometimes they dig through the
trash, too. So, that's kind of a bit of
a pain and they make a mess, so you have
to do something about it.
Bro, brought up bears like they're just
mosquitoes. I mean, they're just trying
to live, but it's Yeah.
Uh there there are black bears. Mostly
black bears, but there are brown bears.
Um
yeah,
I have not seen a brown bear. I think
I've seen a black bear. Uh time dad has
seen a grizzly bear. I think that was a
grizzly. Yeah, pretty sure that's a
grizzly while walking while walking the
dog some time ago and that was um it was
apparently very scary for him. I was
walking up ahead, so I did not know that
that was even happening.
Yeah,
that's scary. I know, right?
So, he was just walking
uh he was just walking the dog and
he didn't even hear anything. They're
just really quiet and then heard like a
branch crack and he turned to the sign
and there's a bear staring straight
towards him and so he wasn't supposed to
do that but he just decided to run
but he survived so that's good.
Yeah.
And then sometimes when you go on walks,
uh, you might accidentally step on a
steak. Uh, not steak. That would be
yummy. You might step on a snake.
I've had that happen twice and had to
prevent someone else from stepping on a
snake. Um, before it was quite
dangerous. And then also there are signs
in the park like don't tie your hair
into a ponytail because an owl might
swoop in and try to snatch your head
because might mistake it for a squirrel.
Yeah.
So I didn't know that there was a sign
like that and that was that was very
interesting.
Do you live in the wild?
Yeah, but it's it's it's interesting.
But you guys do have bear signs, right,
when you're going into parks.
That should be normal.
Or you probably had bears walking around
the school grounds, right?
No,
we have one in the mountains. Oh, that's
weird. Oh.
Um,
I've never asked this for a long time
because I thought that was a common
thing. So, you guys don't have bear
signs in the parks?
Oh.
Oh, that's not a normal thing. I always
thought that was a normal thing.
You guys have had bears walking around
in the school grounds, right?
Cuz back then, uh, we would have
warnings that there'd be bears walking
around and so we wouldn't be able to go
out during recess.
cuz someone might, you know, I don't
know. Who knows what would happen?
>> Oh.
Oh, that's crazy.
Wait, that's so strange.
Have you guys not had like mountain lion
warnings or uh what was it?
You guys have coyotes at least, right?
Okay. Okay. You guys have coyotes. Oh,
cool. Okay. Good. Good. Good.
Yeah, coyotes are more common.
I would see them in the middle of the
night sometimes. I would think um think
to myself, "Ah, there's a there's a dog
walking around." But then the way it
walks is very very different from a dog.
Yeah. So, that's how you can tell.
Wow,
that's a really big dog. It's not really
that big. It just walks
different. It's a little eerie.
I've seen random deers on school
grounds. Oh, yeah.
Yeah, those are pretty common. You would
have like deer signs on the road uh to
make sure that
I think What was it? Oh, yeah. That's a
sign to be like, "Oh, beware of the
deers. Don't hit them." Uh, they're
really common around these parts.
Yeah. Yeah. Deer crossings. Okay. Those
are common. Okay, good.
I'm trying to I'm trying to figure
things out.
H
cuz sometimes
not sometimes I went camping some time
ago years back and it was in the middle
of the forest and nobody was there
just set up tent in the middle of the
forest and there would be deers just
running about and staring at you.
was kind of nice and a little creepy cuz
like sometimes in the middle of the
night you see a little like glint in the
dark and it's probably a deer. Is it a
deer? Is it something else? Who knows?
But um you know, you try not to pay
attention and just look at this guy and
it's pretty awesome and beautiful.
Yeah.
Was there old man's beard? Yeah. Yeah,
there's old man's beard everywhere.
Sometimes um I would go on a walk even
just about a maybe a few weeks ago, 3
weeks ago, I was going on a walk with my
parents and I didn't point it out
because they wouldn't understand. But I
saw old man's beard and was just
thinking old man's beard.
Even when I get dementia, I'll probably
just know what an old man's beard is
when I see it.
That'll be beautiful.
Is that a plant? No, it's a type of
moss. So, you can just see it hanging
off from the branches and you can just
take them off and use it to uh light a
fire better. but also it makes a lot of
smoke so you can use it as a smoke
signal when you're stranded in the
middle of nowhere.
Yeah,
that's practical, right? Yeah, it's
awesome.
How often do I see a snake? I don't
know. Um, no. When I was going on a walk
before uh with my dog, uh I saw a
decapitated snake and it was just
squirming around like a gigantic worm
and I got really scared and I started
running and my dogs you my dog was
usually pretty chill and then uh she saw
that she freaked out because she saw
that I was panicking and so we started
running. Good times.
Yeah. Or like I would just walk around
and then there would be a snake in the
middle of the pavement.
Uh,
that's interesting.
She's an empath dog. Yeah, she's a very
good dog.
Maybe it's a friendly snake. Who knows?
It was a It was a decapitated snake that
was breaking it down.
Pretty crazy.
I'd be so scared. No.
No. None of them are poisonous, so it's
okay.
Seen a rattlesnake in school once. Oh,
yeah. I remember when I went to LA
and I heard rattlesnakes after seeing
signs, but ooh, beware of the
rattlesnakes. And I'd hear their little
rattles and thought it was so cool and
horrifying.
Yeah. And it sounded really close.
Yeah,
I was thinking, wow, that's so cool. But
it also sounds really close. I hope I
don't step on one.
And I didn't step on one. Awesome. Life
is amazing.
Aren't you a thrill seeker?
Not really.
Um,
it's it's eh.
I hope you never have a scary encounter
with a wild animal.
I hope not.
though. If I make it out alive, it'll be
a really cool experience.
You literally went skydiving and I'd do
it again.
If someone would jump with me,
then that would be fine cuz I like to
see other people's reactions, but I
don't really get to see their reactions
because they jump one by one and not at
the same time. So
yeah,
it would be so fun. Oh my goodness.
Yeah. And then
and then if if it's free, I would like
to go to space or you know that little
or like high enough so that you can feel
the gravity and you start floating. That
would be awesome. I want to experience
that.
Staying on the ground. Why not?
It was really expensive. Yeah, that's
why I said if they were free, I would do
it.
Oh my god, with the music from
Interstellar. Oh my god,
life would be so amazing if I can do
that.
Then I have nothing else to ask for in
my life
except 10 billion.
I'm not asking for much. I'm not even
asking for 100 billion. I'm asking for
10 billion. What's Hey, come on. Hey,
like I'm not being too greedy, right?
I'm being pretty reasonable.
Right. I respect the restraint. Thank
you. Cuz like I would I would ask for so
much. I could have been asking for 100
billion. I could be asking for 50
billion. But I'm asking for just 10
billion.
And that would that would help so many
people.
I I I'm pretty modest. Stop. I know.
I'm pretty pretty understanding like
that.
Ooh,
wild horses around the area. Ooh, at the
school you were in. That's awesome.
Wild horses. Where would you have to
live to be able to find wild horses?
Wow.
Hello, Crown. I missed you a lot. It's
been a while since I've been able to see
you live. A few days ago, I went to the
AFO
All for One screening and got reminded
of how amazing you were during that
performance. Very excited for EN 4. Yay.
Yippee.
Yay.
Oh, you're free. Was totally not
missing. You was a big strong crony for
real. For real. But glad to hear you.
Yeah, big [__] Thank you for being
here.
Silly lady. Be watching you laterers
when I'm free. Yippee. Yay.
Yeah,
it's been it's been good as in not
really.
It wasn't bad, but it's just waking up
record uh suffer going like why can't I
do this? Oh my god. And then I think to
myself, why did I choose this?
And then I spend 4 hours and then and
then send it off. And then there's like
six more left and they're all like very
very due.
Overdue and I'm I'm like, "Oh, oh my
god. Oh, it's so over. It's all over. It
is incredibly over. They're going to
kill me. They're literally going to kill
me. They're going to murder me. They are
literally going to murder me and I'm
going to die.
Would you record for 4 hours? Oh, just
just on one thing. And then you move on
to like the other thing. But then by
then my voice is kind of gone and I
can't really record. So, I'm just like,
and then I try to play something, but by
then it's too late and it's just so
I'm too tired to even play something.
And I just go to sleep. I wake up. I
don't even know what I've been up to.
And then my family asks me, "Oh, do you
want to hang out?" And I say, "No, I
can't. I don't work on stuff." And then
I go
I I try to lock in. I'm I'm taking my
meds. I'm locking in, but I'm locking
into the wrong stuff sometimes. And I
go, "Oh, God. No, no, no. Focus on this
because because I'm focusing on this
thing for God knows how long."
Yeah. And then I mean it it's something
that I do have to focus on but like the
priority list is different. It's on a
different level. And so I I do that and
I think yeah I mean I had to do this
eventually I guess but also god damn it
I'm not supposed to do that.
Yeah.
So
that's that's good. I finished so many
things.
Yeah.
Yesterday I was planning on working, but
um I ended up spending time with my
family, which was not so bad. And I uh
I also locked into the wrong thing
again. Um, I mean I had to do it
eventually, but
uh I really didn't have to do that
though.
Yeah,
it was good. I'm really happy. I've just
been so so productive.
I keep saying that, but that's because
it's true. Like sometimes
sometimes I just spend my days lying
around, but then um
but then I just lie down for an hour and
then it kicks in. I go, "Yep, I got to
do it." And I go and do it.
And like honestly, I always knew that I
had like going back to this entire
conversation about the meds. I always
had a feeling that I had it because
growing up like it makes a lot of sense.
It's not something like, "Oh, I'm so
quirky."
And there's like a lot of conversation
going, "Wow, everyone has ADHD." But I
think it's more like there's more
awareness nowadays. But it's just yeah,
it makes a lot of sense because
I
whenever I'm making an appointment,
right, it's hard for me to uh I get
there on time cuz my
my time
um is a bit,
how should I say, more lenient, I think.
Yeah. uh that that should be enough
time, but it's not.
And then there's just no sense of
urgency when it comes to deadlines
um
until the very last minute. So like
growing up um there would be an
assignment that's due and I would not be
panicking until like uh well depending
on what it is. Uh, if it's like just a
normal homework, I would maybe start
working on it at like 2:00 a.m.
the day before. No, the night before
it's due.
Yeah. And then there's a test, right?
I could have been studying for that
test. Or not even Yeah, not even that
test. Final exam, right? if it's a final
exam, it's there's going to be a lot on
the line. No, I spent that time reading
Pokemon Adventures, and that was so
good.
And then at around 3:00 a.m., I thought,
"Oh, I guess I should start working on
it." And then I like study for maybe 3
hours. And then I go to sleep at around
6:00 a.m. And then I think to myself,
"Yeah, I think that should be enough."
Um when I wake up I'll study a bit more
but you do have to sleep uh so that your
retention span is better and you got to
let this uh
stuff that you learn ruminate in your
sleep. And so I just go to I just go to
bed
and then I wake up panicking like an
hour before 30 minutes before
and I'm just staring at all the notes
that I've taken hoping that something
will stick and I try to write things on
my skin in hopes that something would
work. not cheating, but like you know
cuz the way I
um studied was that I would just write
everything on a note. It doesn't even
have to be clean. I just need to write
like I don't even need to under
understand it. I just need to copy all
the definitions. So
yeah. So I just write it. I don't even
need a flash card. I don't think
flashcards really help because I just
need to write it down.
Yeah,
writing notes help you absorb the info.
So, I already wrote down like I I
already took my notes. I'm just copying
those notes.
Yeah. So, I'm just writing it down
repeatedly until it gets into my head
and hopefully there's muscle memory that
follows after.
Yeah. And sometimes
uh when I would get into
taking the test and everything, I don't
remember, right? Obviously, I don't
remember most of the things, half the
things. So, what I do is I close my
eyes. I try to pretend I have
photographic memory and I think about
the time where I opened up the textbook
and highlighted it and I would think
very very hard.
There were there were a few times where
it worked.
Like one maybe one one time where it
worked and I felt like a genius
but most of the time it didn't work.
Yeah.
Good times.
>> Yeah.
And then if there was something let's
say an 18page paper
uh that I would start panicking maybe
maybe a day and a half. So, I would
start panic like panicking around
nighttime
at around 12
12:00 a.m.
And so what I would do is uh have all
the things that I'd want to include in
my bibliography,
uh my cited works, whatever,
and I would grab them
and
and then just call it a night.
And then I I take a shower. I do this
whole routine
uh almost like a ritual to get my
mindset
clean and fresh. And I turn on a
diffuser
and just sit there
until
I'm done basically. And then I take like
a 2hour nap and then I keep working on
it
and then submit it at exactly
I would submit my first my supposedly
final copy of the first version uh at
around 11:00 p.m. And then I would
upload like five or six more uh until
the deadline that is 11:59 p.m.
or Well, yeah. 11:59 p.m. Yeah.
Oh, good times. And I would do that
every single time. Every single time.
And then there was this other time where
I submitted my paper very last minute.
Um
I think the teacher was almost about to
leave and I I handed it in right right
on time.
Surprisingly, I never got any late
penalties,
but I had to run all the way from I
don't know the entire way to school just
to submit it. And then after that, I was
so tired that I lied on the ground.
And then the teacher was just staring at
me very pitifully.
Good times.
Yeah, but just just like thinking about
all those incidents,
it kind of makes sense
in public like that. Yeah. I mean,
nobody was really around.
Yeah, nobody was really around except
for the teacher. Um,
stepped out of the the room and
everything just so that I can hand it
in.
Yeah,
I I like that teacher.
I hope he's alive.
He was really nice teacher.
Ah,
yeah.
Was
was he really old? That he was he was a
bit old. Kind of reminded me of um
Who was it? Froto's uncle from Lord of
the Rings.
Yeah. Kind of endearing.
Yeah.
Yeah. Bilbo. Bilbo Baggins. Yeah.
Probably that one.
Yeah.
And his tests were actually pretty
reasonable. I I liked I liked his class,
man.
Oh, man.
I hope he didn't retire.
I really hope he didn't retire.
A class you actually liked?
No, I didn't really like that class. It
was just that it was a good teacher.
Yeah. No. No. He can't retire. No, he
can't.
No. No.
What if What if I What if I want to take
take his class again? I don't know.
No. No. No. He's got to keep working.
He's got to wait for me.
No, no. He if he retired, I'm going to
have to go up to him and ask him to come
back just just for me.
For how long?
Like maybe I don't know 3 years.
Uh maybe like just work for 3 years and
then and then he can take a break.
>> Yeah,
man.
Those were those were good times.
Just one semester. No, no, not not one
semester. It's got to be three years.
Three years.
You say everything was good times.
Yeah, because they're in the past for a
reason. It's kind of like liking Super
Mario Sunshine.
Uh you go and think back on it, you
think, "Wow, that was a really good
game." And then you go and play it
yourself actually and go to that
watermelon stage and you would start
hating that game so so badly. or that
that freaking area where they take away
flood and they have this funky music
kicking in and then
they just keep going at it. I hate that
level. I not level. I hate those levels.
Yeah. But then that watermelon stage,
the worst thing ever. Absolutely
terrible.
And then the Lion King SNES one, you
think, "Oh, yeah, that was really cool."
You know, graphics were nice and
everything and oh, they had their own
rendition of all the music from Lion
King and then you play it yourself. You
want to throw everything and burn
something. I don't know, light your
entire house on fire.
I hated I hated that one so bad for some
reason. I
I had I was feeling nostalgic for that
game for some reason cuz I did pretty
decently and just can't wait to be king.
And so I thought, "Oo yeah, I want to go
play it." Um it was terrible. I don't
know what I was thinking.
And then
the last part that I played was Lakuna
Matata.
Hated it.
I think I went far enough to the final
stage, but I quit.
But um
yeah.
Uh, but that was through the power of
infinite reloads because I was not going
to play that game from scratch.
>> Did she at least get the adult Simba?
Yeah, the the final stage
and the lions there were absolutely
nightmares. I hated it so much.
Oh, thank you, Ted Conway. Thank you.
Congrats on your new found freedom. Yay.
Hopefully, I will not let this pile up
again. Maybe I can lock in normally like
a normal person.
The study and homework stuff have been
very embarrassingly relatable, and I
started taking meds about it just a
month ago. Hope it's not too late for
me. I just never too late for you. If
it's If it's late for you, then I'm
going to It's over for me.
It's over for me.
Oh, it's so over for me.
>> Well, thank you for the recommendations.
Those are cool.
Yeah.
What was I talking about? Nostalgia.
I don't know how I got on that topic of
um rage games, but I think it was
something about nostalgia.
Yes.
Oh, yeah. And then they they ported the
Lion King game with like two other
games. I think that was Aladdin and
something else.
Uh
I don't remember. But they're all very
terrifying.
They probably made that game to be like,
"Oh, I bet people miss it."
H seems like everyone's having too much
of a good time. Just getting more like a
bad time. Oh, I know how to make it
worse.
Yeah. Yeah. Let's just port the game to
the Switch. Oh, what a wonderful idea.
Yeah. Hated it. Hated it so much. Even
Mega Man. I played Oh, yeah. I played
Mega Man cuz I was having a I had so
many good memories about it. That's
because I only cleared the first stage
and I didn't know how to save the game
back then. So, every single time I would
just be really good at the first stage.
And besides, that wasn't really my go-to
game anyway.
Oh, hello.
Welcome.
Yeah. And then and then I was like, "Oh,
yeah. It was such a good time. Let's
let's go play it." And I was really
fascinated for the first stage and
everything like, "Oh my god, that's so
nostalgic."
And then
I mean I would still play
I'm still open to playing other Mega Man
games. Uh I think it has its charm to
it.
Um
yeah, but that was time.
No, it's not. It's not even about like
seeing the appeal. I would actually play
it. Um,
definitely. If I didn't like the game, I
would have hidden it, but I did not hide
it.
Yeah.
What about Battle Network? What's a
Battle Network?
I don't know what that is.
Is that like
is that the one for Blizzard
her IRL backlog of games? Oh yeah, I
finished Kuloniku.
I 100% in Kuloniku.
It was uh it was pretty good. It went up
to like 138 days or something. I don't
remember.
But I 100%ed it.
Uh, how'd you like it? It was cool. It
was It was interesting.
I romanced everyone. I mean, yeah. I
mean, you know, I 100%ed the game, so I
uh romanced everyoneish.
It's not really romancing. It's just
more like
getting extra cut scenes from everyone.
Did you play Dave the Diver yet? I did.
Uh, not the DLC though. I haven't played
any of the DLCs.
Actually, there was only one DLC. Those
were just extra editions. Yeah, I didn't
play the extra editions.
The jungle DLC. Yeah,
maybe once I'm done
working on all this stuff, as in just
one more, just one more, then I'll be so
happy and I can just go back to playing.
It will be amazing.
Have I played Dynasty Warriors? Um,
I think I did. I think I played it off
of um
someone who had a PSP or was it a PS VA?
And I saw them playing it. It looked
really fun. Well, back then I thought
anyone who had a PSP or a PS Vita were
rich.
Cuz how else would you be able to carry
around a handheld like that? Wow. How
Wow. That's That's amazing.
You're so You're so well off.
Veto was so cheap for a while. Was it? I
don't know. It was still pretty
expensive for me.
How How much was the PSP? Whoa.
But then again, I didn't grow up with a
PlayStation or an Xbox. I grew up with
Nintendo.
And that was still wonderful. Innocent
wait hold on.
Oh,
I guess it's not just Nintendo cuz I
think I remember playing Dragon Ball for
some reason.
Well, yeah. I didn't play Dragon Ball.
Okay. Well, I I guess I played Dragon
Ball, but then there was someone else
who really liked playing Dragon Ball.
There's Dragon Ball games on Nintendo.
Oh, really? Okay. I didn't know that.
Have you watched Dragon Ball? Yeah. Had
a VHS tape. Uh, it was the one with
uh I don't know Dragon Ball that well. I
um know very basic general ideas of it,
but
it was uh I think Kid Buu. Kid Buu.
Evil.
Yeah, evil guy is Kid Buu, I think. And
he was absorbing everyone.
Yeah. And then I think that was the
episode where in the end he absorbed
Vegeta.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I I don't know Dragon Ball that well.
Yeah. Yeah. The the evil one. Oh, is
that called Super Boo? Okay. It was like
a skinny cuz there's like a Majin Buu is
the nice guy, but then there's like an
evil one where he slims down and starts
absorbing everyone.
>> Yeah.
I remember watching that and thinking,
damn, this is so exciting. Where's the
next episode? And there there was
nothing. It was just that one VHS for
Dragon Ball.
Let's see.
Which Which one was it? Kid Bu. Oh, it
was Kid Buu. That Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. It was featuring Kid Buu. Hey, I
was right. It is Kid Boo.
And you were trying to correct me.
Yeah.
It It was the It was a short one. Yeah.
What? What's a super boo?
Yeah. No, it was not this one.
Kid boo didn't absorb anyone.
What the heck did I watch then?
What? What? What did I watch? But I
swear it was this one. It was this form.
Didn't he like eat the robots? The what
was it? The androids. And then he gets
more and more different. No, that was
Cell.
I'm I told you I didn't really watch
Dragon Ball.
I I corrected myself. Okay. See, I have
a very general idea of Dragon Ball.
I I told you. I don't I'm not even
laring. I don't know. I have a I just
have a very general idea. I've done a
wiki dive of Dragon Ball and I still
don't understand.
But I but then again, I've also done a
wiki dive for Aangelion and I still
don't understand. There are a lot of
things I don't understand in general.
Yeah,
it was like
back when I was watching
bit more of the Dragon Ball stuff that
was uh
when Goku was a kid and he still had a
tail and it was giving Um,
what was what was was her name?
It it had the art style. Um, I know it's
the same creator of uh Dr. Slump.
Yeah. But the art style was more like
that. And it was
Kid Goku
and then Chi-Chi.
And then the strongest guy back then was
Yamcha. Super ironic
cuz that guy just disappeared after
everyone got power scaled to infinity
and beyond.
So that was um
what I was uh watching back then. Not
too much. And then for some reason he
turned into a gigantic
uh monkey when I think there was a red
moon or something.
Yeah. And then I stopped watching at
around the time that Shenron appeared.
Um, for some reason I remember seeing
Shenron.
That's about it.
And I think Oh, yeah. And then Master
Roshi was showing off um one Dragon Ball
that he had.
Yeah. And then later on I would just I'd
pass by and he slowly grew up.
That that was me cuz you know I'm I'm
going through life. I'm the warden of
time and the one day he's just a kid.
Other times I go back he's growing up. I
come back he's dead. I come back he's
back to life for some reason. And then
he's throwing a gigantic spirit bomb cuz
he's believing in the power of
friendship and everybody's giving him uh
trust and love and belief in him or
whatever the trust of humanity and he
blasts the spirit bomb to something and
then he dies again
and then and then he comes back to life.
I don't like what's the point of dying
if you're just going to come back to
life. I don't really understand. And
then um they start having like like
Dragon Ball Z, Dragon Ball Z GT, Dragon
Ball does some other letters
and then first it's Gohan and then
you're thinking, "Oh, Gohan. Oh, that's
pretty cute." And then Gohan grows up
and he he's the main character now,
which I think, oh, interesting. Oh yeah.
And then there's this guy named Satan
and he's very obnoxious and annoying.
And then he still gets all the credit.
He still gets away with it. Makes me
angry.
Oh yeah. And then there was Piccolo.
Piccolo. Piccolo. Yeah.
Uh way way back. Yeah. He used to be
really cool too. And then he also got
power scaled to
uh to infinity and beyond.
And then
yeah, and then Gohan gets into a
relationship. I'm like, "Oh, okay. I
guess that's happening." And this is
just me passing by, right? Um and it's
it's like on the the show is on. I'm
like, "Oh, okay, cool."
And then one day I'm just passing by
again and he's he has a kid. It's like
Goten or something and they look exactly
the same. They're basically clones. What
the heck?
Oh yeah. And then there there was like
what was it? The other one with Future
Trunks or something.
Oh, Goten's his brother. I thought that
was his son.
Well, anyway, point is they're like
cloning each other. It's exactly the
same. Insane.
Oh, yeah. And then Vegeta got married,
which didn't really make any sense.
How could he get married to a human, no
less? I thought he was super racist.
Pan is the daughter. Oh, yeah. Pan's the
uh the the wife of Gohan.
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
And then
see I'm I I know things
like very general idea but I I know
things like Supercell
he's absorbing bunch of androids
and then
I think at the Cell arc, Gohan
uh first got his Super Saiyan form cuz
he was scared of uh turning into or
well, he was scared in general. He's
like, "Hey, I'm so scared." Like he
turns into a Super Saiyan
perfect cell, whatever the Super Cell.
And then and then like he's suddenly
like he's just a kid, but he's suddenly
like super strong and he's like face
maxing. His face card is like all there
all of a sudden. And I'm thinking, "Wow,
that's crazy."
And then
uh yeah, that happened.
And then the kid boo thing. I have no
idea. I think that was towards the end
or something. No idea.
Why is it that every single time someone
turns Super Saiyan, they start like face
maxing?
They're they start mogging. Everyone
starts mogging.
Yeah. And then they can fuse like
Vegito. I have no idea. I don't even
know where that even comes in. But
they're sharing an earring. I don't even
know where they got that earring. But
they're like, you know, doing the weird
pose and they're like, "Oh, we're going
to fuse all of a sudden to fight this
whatever thing."
Yeah.
And I'm thinking to myself, "Oh, wow.
The the earring, it's uh kind of
fruity."
Yeah. And uh then they start fighting
and I don't know how they're able to be
in control of their body so well.
Yeah.
I uh I don't really remember. And then I
think his hair turned red at some point.
I don't really know why.
Those are the earrings of the gods. Oh,
yeah. From the the Piccolo people.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Cuz the Piccolo people
uh bring Goku back to life or something.
There's a there's an old Piccolo and old
Piccolo can talk to dead Goku for some
reason.
Nomecians
nom nomians.
Yeah, the Piccolo people.
Yeah. So, and then and then then the the
King Piccolo, old Piccolo. Uh I think he
had a really long white cape. I don't
really remember anymore. I think he was
in like a little like spaceship looking
thing. Maybe not. Or maybe he was in a
big tower. I don't know. Was one of the
two. And he's like just trying his best
to be important and everything. Um.
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. And then uh Shenron just kind of
disappears.
Uh
I don't know. Sometimes he comes back.
He's not really important, come to think
of it.
Oh yeah. And then free Frieza. Frieza
comes in
um out of nowhere. I guess he's like the
final boss. I think he doesn't really
come in that often. Come to think of it.
I think he has like multiple forms. I
thought he was a girl,
but he's not.
And um
yeah, he he comes in he comes in from
somewhere and he brags about how he
killed Goku's dad.
What was his name? Bardock.
Was that his brother? I have no idea.
And then
and then uh what was it? You remember
Bardock? Yeah. See, I I know very
general things.
Yeah. And then Bardock was like a really
awesome Super Saiyan warrior, whatever.
And he had a beautiful wife and
everything.
um
who's usually not the type of person to
save people and whatever, but uh he he
wanted to save his kid. Kind of out of
character a bit. And then he gets killed
by Frieza and stuff.
Yeah. And then
uh and then he gets killed anyway.
Frieza brags about it to Goku, I guess.
And then Radits is just I think he's
like a Frieza lackey
and he's bragging.
Yeah,
he's a coward.
Uh
um and they all have their tails. Oh
yeah, they have they have their tails.
Yeah, the Super Saiyan people, they have
their tails wrapped around like a little
belt. Um,
I don't know why Goku cut his off. I
think it was an accident. I have no
idea. Oh, yeah. He cut his tail off when
he was younger. That I I think I
remember that episode cuz it was really
disgusting
and it was like wiggling around like a
worm. I think that was really gross.
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And then later on, way
way way later on, um
uh the the what was it? The little like
woman next to Yamcha.
Uh she had a little cat,
a talking cat, talking blue cat.
And
I forget her name. She turned she's a
grandma now.
Yeah. But then she suddenly turns young
and then has a romantic relationship
with uh someone
uh who is very young. And I think I
remember the internet crashing out about
that. I was like, "Oh, weird.
And then I decided to just kind of step
out of that entire thing cuz I was just
a third person watching uh from far away
and everybody was crashing out and was
like, "Oh, is this right? Is this
wrong?" And there's me not knowing
anything. So I'm like, "Oh,
I don't know.
Things are happening, I guess." But this
was like way way way way later.
Yeah. See, I I know some like general
stuff.
Oh my god, chat's not working anymore.
You know, a lot a lot like very
generally.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Maybe it'll work eventually.
Yeah. And then at the very end of it,
uh, Majin Buu, um, well, that's the
final one, so I'm not going to spoil it
too much. Majin Buu has like a you know
I'm not going to say it but the things
happen magical things and then Goku is
like oh I'm going to show you the world
and then that's it.
Yeah.
See, I know things.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Already spoiled. It's okay. It's not
really spoiling if
if half of them are wrong.
It's okay.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
There there were people getting rage
baited and I'm doing my job very
successfully. Awesome.
Yeah. Yeah.
So that's that's all I know about Dragon
Ball
yeah.
And I'm falling for it. Nice. Nice.
Nice.
Can you badly explain bleach?
Oh, yeah.
So, the anime was misleading the love
interest
uh because the anime development team
and the manga artist uh couldn't
communicate properly and uh they
actually hated each other.
And the anime development team was
supporting Rukia's love line, but uh the
original creator was a lot more
supportive and hinting towards Oriheime.
Yeah, it's true. It's true.
Look it up.
Yeah. And that's why the manga artists
didn't really like the development team.
And also, uh, there's this guy who
closes his eyes all the time. Um, but
then when his eyes open, the eye color
was wrong and
the the creator kind of roasted the
anime development team uh by like
drawing it
by himself with the correct eye color
after it was released or something.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. They hated each other.
Yeah.
So that's what I know about bleach.
How do you know about that? That's I
know very general things.
Yeah.
Why is it called bleach then?
Uh
cuz like you use crushed bones to bleach
things back in the days and it's to uh
the
the death will bleach the
world
and stuff
and
Yeah.
So, like
I don't Okay. To be very honest, I don't
know. Bleach.
I'm going to do a disclaimer.
Um
Oh, yeah. I am rage baiting. Awesome.
Okay.
Ra Oh yeah. Awesome. Rage bait segment.
So,
what I know, Bleach,
Bleach
uh revolves around this kid named
Ichigo,
and he has orange hair, and I think he's
a delinquent.
Um, for some reason, I'm making things
up as I go. So, he just uh goes around
minding his own business, being a little
delinquent, and then bumps into Rukia,
who is a Soul Society member, and she
can't use her powers or something. So,
she gives it to Ichigo or something. I
don't really know. And then Ichigo is
like, "Okay." And that he becomes a
temporary soul society member and he
goes around killing monsters. Wait,
wait. Am I right?
Really? Am I right? I didn't know that.
Really?
Oh, that's crazy.
Oh, is he a delinquent?
Is he actually a delinquent?
Oh, I just assume cuz like you know he
kind of gives off the delinquent vibe.
Maybe he like dyed his hair orange
because he's a delinquent too. I don't
know.
Oh, his mom died. I don't know that.
Yeah. Okay.
Rookie has no powers.
I just assumed because I didn't see her
using her powers at all. And she was
always the damsel in distress. Uh, but
she was very much wellliked.
Oh, that's crazy. Wait, how did he get
his powers then? Okay, that's spoilers.
Anyway, he goes around doing his stuff
and then uh Rukia
uh Rukia gets in trouble with the upper
soul society members or something and
then she's going to get into trouble and
Ichigo tries his best to
uh help her and stuff. And then the the
guy that has his eyes closed opens his
eyes and starts uh destroying him, I
guess. And then
and then obviously he probably can't
beat them because they're super strong,
but that they're like, "Yes, you know
what? I was going to take away your
powers because you're technically not
dead and only dead people can be part of
this. But you're pretty capable. So, I
guess you can be part of the Soul
Society member for now.
Um,
wait.
Is it? I don't know.
Really?
Oh, are you
close enough?
I don't know.
Okay. So, like I don't know what happens
afterwards. And then there's this uh
I don't know how he gets this, but
there's like an evil shade. Uh oh. Oh,
holo.
Yeah. And he has a mask, but it's like
his evil the evil Ichigo. And he's like,
"Oh, I'm so evil." Like, "Oh, uh, you
got to destroy me." And then he's like,
"Oh, no. He's so strong. I'm making this
up as I go. He's probably thinking, "Oh,
how could he be so strong?" Oh, it's
because
I'm you and you are me and I know you.
Ah, I know you best and all your trauma.
I don't know. It probably reminds him of
his trauma or something. Probably his
dead mom, which I just found out. Um,
and he's getting really triggered.
Ichigo is having like a lot of trigger
time and um uh he probably has more
in-depth flashback with his mom or
something with his family and then
through that he gets like a little
character development arc and goes uh uh
you know what and then he like gets
really powerful and the hollow is
probably going oh when did you get so
strong all all of a sudden crazy and
then it probably gets destroyed.
But then I keep seeing this hollow
character, so he probably comes back
somehow.
Uh
I don't know. Maybe
people really like this character. So
maybe he comes back as like a little
stand some somehow.
Maybe maybe he like gets this as like a
new ability or like a sidekick. I don't
really know.
And then
yeah
stuff.
Yeah.
So after that,
um
I don't really know what's I don't even
know what the final boss is. I don't
even know what the mid boss is. Um,
and then they probably have a lot of
filler episodes. There's probably the
obligatory beach episode and then the
onset episode probably.
Um,
maybe. I don't know.
and then they fight this ultimate boss,
the one that threatens the entire world
and the soul society. I'm really making
this up cuz I have no idea at this
point. The holo thing, I only knew that
there was a holo character and that's
it. This other one, I have no idea. Um
there's this big gigantic boss. There's
like a mid boss probably cuz there's
always that oh like you know I'm the
henchman of the final boss and
yeah I'm the henchman of the final boss
and he gets stronger probably unlocks
new abilities along the way and then um
yeah
and then encounters this final boss
and this final boss guess
I don't know is his dad I don't know
like a family member
like maybe that's why he's like able to
get soul society powers or something I
don't know
maybe it's genetics I don't know
so like
yeah So, he's probably crashing out
being like, "Oh my god, I can't believe
you're my dad." Or, I don't know, mom. I
don't know. Probably not mom. I mean, I
guess mom cuz mom's dead, right? I guess
maybe her body was just I don't freaking
know. But then,
I mean, he probably lived his life being
alone. So, it's either mom or dad. So
like he probably has a really big
misunderstanding or the wrong agenda.
They start duking things out and then
probably going like, "Oh my god, where
were you?" Let's just say, "Dad, where
were you when mom was uh suffering? When
we were suffering and you were just out
there doing your own thing and just
being so focused in your own stuff.
you're so selfish. And then he's just
very messed in the head and going,
"Haha, you should you should join me or
something." I don't know. And then
and then and then it's like gone and she
gets super powerful and uh defeats the
dad or something and dad's going, "Oh,
you know what? I'm so sorry. Um
so sorry for everything."
And then he dies. And now he's
traumatized.
Well, not traumatized.
And then
and I don't know where Ori comes in and
all of this, but she's probably pulling
a Hinata and just trying to be a little
more supportive and everything. And that
probably hints towards it hints towards
something. And then there's like a
little time skip with everyone being
happy or whatever.
Yeah.
And then they have a really good ending
overall.
Yeah.
Ori does a lot more than Hinata and I'm
a Hinata fan.
Yeah,
but I don't know. I don't know bleach at
all.
Yeah.
Why is my cat crying?
Yeah. And then I remember that people
were like angry about uh this whole who
Ichigo ended up with and I'm just there
watching cuz I don't know what's going
on.
Yeah.
So
yeah, maybe I should go check it out.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You might be disappointed if you do. Oh,
you guys were just lying to me when you
were going, "Oh, you're so right. You're
so correct. Am I wrong? I've been wrong
all this time. You're just encouraging
me to say all this random stuff that's
not even true.
You let the first half right. Okay.
Oh, the the first half's right. Oh,
cool. Awesome.
I'm 40% right. Awesome. Okay.
probably real in one timeline. Yeah.
Oh, I got the dad part right. Oh, dad is
evil.
Really?
>> Oh, dad is not evil. Oh.
So, do they fight?
>> Oh, the genetic parts. Okay. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
You know,
I don't really watch Fairy Tale. Like,
this just like as a on a random note, I
didn't watch Fairy Tale, but you know
what? I watched and read
Rave Master. That was so freaking good.
And it was so rewarding to see the uh
the artist get better and better with
the art. So good. I loved Rave Master.
Yeah.
And then I saw
that the there were some characters that
were similar like Blue for example
and other other characters that looked
similar.
I was actually kind of surprised because
I think the uh creator
uh fairy tale and rave master uh was
like
uh Oda's pupil. I think
I think that's really cool.
Yeah, he he learned under him or
something.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I I think it was Let me double check.
Oh,
they never worked together. I see. Okay.
It was just a rumor. Okay. I heard that
they were like, you know,
like disciples, like pupil or something,
but I guess not. Okay,
good.
It's a widpread rumor. Okay.
Hey, that's why it's important to fact
check.
Anyway,
Brave Master, it was so good. I was
watching the anime and then I couldn't
watch the anime anymore, so I found the
manga and started reading. It was so
freaking good, man.
I really really liked Lucy as a
character, which is rare cuz I rarely
like any female characters.
That's not true. I like some some female
characters.
Would usually not like characters like
that. Yeah, I read all of Ravemaster. It
was really good.
Yeah,
there's a Lucy and Raithmaster, too. Oh,
there's a Lucy in Fairy Tale. I did not
know that.
You guys should read Rave Master. The
art gets better and better over time and
it's so cool to see that. I really love
seeing things where you can see that the
artist is honing their skills.
Yeah, that was so good, man. Ah.
Ah. Brave master. So good.
Eden zero. Oh, I don't know what that
is.
I will read rave if you read Chainsaw
Man. I thought about reading Chainsaw
Man cuz like you know a lot of people
liked it and I knew some of my friends
were reading it so I thought that was
pretty cool. Also it ended so I thought
why not. Yeah,
but then again, I wanted to watch not
watch, I wanted to read Tokyo Gold, too,
but didn't have time.
I uh
I think I stopped reading.
No, wait, hold on. Okay. So, I watched
the anime
um before the time skip
and I was reading Re Tokyo Guru Re
and I stopped.
Yeah.
And Tokyo had really nice art, too.
Oh, so so nostalgic. Oh my god. You
should watch Ajin, too. Isn't that the
3D animated one? And people were talking
about it going, "Oh, the story is really
good. It's just that I wish the
animation was done differently.
You see, see I know things. I I know
things.
I I know very general things.
So like whenever someone's talking about
it, I can go, "Oh, that Haha. Yeah.
And then I can get away with it until
someone starts asking really indepth
questions, which has not happened yet.
Really good. Usually, it's just, "Oh, I
like this character." And I go, "Oh,
cool. Yeah, the the blue-haired one,
right?" They go, "Yeah." They they start
talking about it. I just listen.
Yeah. I mean, I don't pretend like I
know it obviously, but it's just more so
that they don't feel awkward in talking
about it
cuz I I'm a bit of an empath.
And then you hit them with the Oh, yeah.
I saw some of it.
I mean is is
um ish not really.
I just say oh yeah I I saw parts of it
on Twitter.
Yeah.
Never went back for it. No. That's
That's not true.
Never heard of it. It's the most painful
thing you can hear. Yeah, I I know.
Which is why I don't do that cuz I'm
nice.
I'm nice like that.
Who watches anime on Twitter? You know,
clips or like people do screenshots and
they're like, "Oh my god, I can't
believe this is happening
or like there's a meme going around." So
that's that's how I know.
Yeah.
Yeah. But the animes
that I used to watch, they were
they're
they're on the older side.
It's been a bit.
It's been a really long bit.
Like
Muloka Majika, that's like more new. Um,
Erase was really good.
Ozamanga Dio was really good. Yeah, that
was so that was so good, guys. Oh my
god.
Um,
how do I sign it? Oh, Card Captor
Sakura. Yeah, I read all of uh Card
Capture Sakura.
That was pretty good. I like that one.
Except towards the end it got kind of
weird
as in like it focused too much on
romance and also the art style changed
or in high school host club. I think I
told you the story behind this one. Um
sad sad times.
Let's see. I'm gonna I'm gonna see what
did what did I watch?
Uh
oh. Yeah,
I finished watching Assassination
Classroom. Yeah,
that was good.
I watched all of Blood Plus.
That was sad.
Uh, let's see.
Oh, and I read all of uh Mahin
Gloo. That was pretty good.
Do you know Tokyo Miumu?
Isn't that the magical girls that are
cats?
Sia the best girl.
Sia.
Oh, yeah. Sia. Yeah. The main character.
Yes. Okay. I was like, are you talking
about the other twin? Cuz she was really
evil.
I think her name was Diva.
She She was so evil.
I
I watched
uh
Oh,
I watched Doram.
Hey, Doram was really good.
Oh, Jamacho to me. That was so good,
guys. It was amazing. It was so cute.
I thought magical girls were just so
awesome. And then I watched Maho Shojo
Moka Majika because um there was this
guy online. I I wasn't friends with him.
We were just in the same um circle I
guess and there were a lot of people but
then this one guy uh he just kept
talking about how good Maho Shojo Moka
Majika is and I looked at it and I don't
really like the art style either and I
was a bit judgmental
going like
this and and then it was like a
screenshot where like they're
it's it's
they were naked. Okay. It was like
supposed to be touching or something,
but it was like, you know, when they
transform and they're like a bit
temporarily naked. It was like that. And
that was the screenshot. And so I was
thinking, oh, um, this looks really
uh why why are you going around like
telling everyone that you're watching
this? This is kind of this for kids like
like Doramy level and then I watched it.
I was thinking
yeah yeah yeah
then I watched it. It was pretty messed
up. I liked it kind of awesome
but I never admitted it to that person
because I did not like that person.
Um, we just
again we don't really talk to each other
just just same circle.
Didn't really talk to each other.
But it was pretty good.
Can you badly explain Detective Conan?
Dude,
you don't even need to badly explain it.
It's just you can summarize Detective
Conan
in four sentences in a paragraph. That's
it.
Sorry, not even the paragraph. Three
sentences.
Oh, and I watched um
Blue Exorcist. Oh, no. Exorcist.
And then
there's this thing called da da da.
That was pretty cute.
And then there's this thing called
you Sky Sugar. That was pretty cute,
too. Ending was really freaking sad.
Yeah.
Oh my god. And there was Angelic Layer.
Why is Angelic Layer not on here? I
watched the living
stuff out of that.
And then I watched a bit of Akaska.
Um because that they had the VHS at my
cousin's house. So I watched that.
I think that was in Japanese for some
reason.
That was in America.
None of them spoke Japanese. Why did
they have that? Come to think of it.
What the heck? Where' they get that
from? Oh, wait. Yeah.
No, no. Okay, I remember why. Okay, that
makes sense.
Oh, I want to watch Serial Experiments.
Lane
line.
Yeah.
Oh, Gintama. Gentama was super good. Oh,
I'm trying to
uh
in my drop list. Uh but things I
technically watched and uh that was Ata
Sheni.
That was pretty good.
Season one of Code Guos Crayon Shinshan
Dimmon.
Oh,
Phantom Thief Jean Ka Jean. Heck yeah.
That was pretty good.
How could you draw Guos? I I first came
across Guos. Uh, Nagios, Code Gio. Um,
season two. I watched season two, but
not season 1.
And then I watched a bit of season 1. I
think I went halfway.
Well, I think season one was a bit too
painful, so I didn't like painful and
like emotionally painful, so I don't
want to finish it.
Yeah. But I like I like season two.
Uh
yeah.
And then McCross. Macros. F. There's
that.
Detective Conan.
Amai Nikki. Right.
Aon man
Ronma. I didn't finish watching the
anime, but I finished reading the manga.
There's Sword Art Online. And then
there's Yakat Japan.
That was pretty good.
Um,
right.
I used to Oh, yeah.
Yamura and the Seven Witches. I read the
manga for that for a bit and then it got
released into an anime and then I didn't
watch it anymore or read for that
matter.
I was saying Seya Lost Canvas.
Ah, I'm still going to finish reading
that eventually.
No, wait. I think I watched it.
Yeah, I'm going to finish watching that
eventually.
Oh my god. Senu.
Oh, these are so nostalgic.
Yeah, Senu.
Senue 2. I watched that. Oh, I finished
that.
Senu was funny. Yeah, most of these are
way before my time. Hey, you. No, that's
not true. You stop saying it like that.
You you I uh I watched the first season
of Kake Gurui. Kake Gurui
Tikashi. I think I watched most of that
the first season.
Yeah. See, that's recent. I really like
Devil Man Crybaby. Oh my god,
look at this. Look at Look at all the
list here. Death No, Death Parade. Devil
Man Cry Baby.
Oh, so good.
God, the song was so freaking good. And
then it wasn't the song for like like
opening or ending. It just didn't come
out. And I was thinking, damn, they have
this banger music. I remember when all
the memes were coming out with that
song. It was so good. That song was so
good
and it didn't come out. So I was
thinking, damn, the why are they sitting
on this? And then the song did come out
and one of the darker moments
briefly, but it was still a banger.
Yeah. And with Death Parade, uh, Light
Yagami did feature as like a bit of an
Easter egg. That was pretty cool.
A, look at this. Digimon Adventure.
Digimon Adventure movie. Dormon.
Oh, yeah. I watched this one. I watched
the Don origin story.
How do you say this in English?
I have no idea.
It's Don.
Yeah, this was the Dorim on origin story
and it was really good.
Crony is a giant fan. No, no, no, no.
I I am more of a I like Dion more.
And besides, like every everybody else,
they were bullies, you know? Like, sure,
they were apparently so-called friends,
but they were so bullies. They were
hitting each other. like they were
trying to have their little redemption
arc, but that doesn't stop the that that
doesn't change the fact that they're
like still bullies and they like hit him
so much. If you read the manga, damn,
they beat him up really good. So that's
why it always made me a bit
uncomfortable because they grow up and
they're all adults and they're all
pretending to be good friends. And I
mean, it's good that they went past that
and still became friends, but they never
asked for forgiveness. It's just a bit
I don't know, kind of rubs me the wrong
way.
Yeah, if only he apologized, it would
have been nice. But he never really
apologized. They just kind of went over
it. And I know it's just a kid show, but
still that's not really nice.
>> Yeah.
Like if only they just apologized, I
think I would have been like a lot more
better about it.
Yeah.
See
what is this one? Oh, that's Kiki's
Delivery Service.
I watched a lot of the Detective Conan
movies.
Oh, that's kind of unexpected. I watched
the most recent one, too. Um because
they had it on uh the the airplane.
Uh
I watched Detective Conan
movie. Number two, The 14th Target.
Number three, The Last Wizard of the
Century. Oh god, freaking Kao Kid. So
awesome. And then four, Captured in Her
Eyes.
And then five, Countdown to Heaven. And
then six, The Phantom of Baker Street.
This is the best one. Personally, I I
think this is the best movie ever
in Detective Conan. And then there's
movie 13, The Raven Chaser.
Yeah.
So good.
You guys don't know Phantom of the Baker
Street. So good, guys. Oh my god.
You guys have to watch that.
That That was That was my favorite.
Oh yeah,
wolf children.
Yeah,
I know
a lot of people liked Wolf Children,
but I wasn't exactly a fan.
And I think it's okay to, you know,
everyone's entitled to their own
opinion, so that's that's okay.
Yeah. You Oh, you really like that one.
That's That's good.
I
um
it has a little something for everyone.
Yeah.
And I think
that's okay.
Yeah.
No, it's not cuz of No, it's not because
of that. It's not cuz of the husband.
It's more because of um
towards the ending I guess.
Yeah.
What was the ending?
It's
Yeah.
Like
I mean
I'm not saying it's a bad movie. It it's
just like you know people like it and I
can I can respect that.
Yeah.
She doesn't even want to talk about No,
it's like
Yeah. like I can see
I'm sure
the animation is very nice. Um
and like the the beginning I think was
really um good
in the middle.
Well, like you know not everyone can
like everything, right?
So there's there's that.
Yeah. Oh, but the Latio the Latas Latios
movie was really good.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That Oh, really
good. I love that.
Oh, the director that did Girl Who Left
Her Time. Okay. Okay. But I didn't like
that one. I like the girl who leapt
through time. That was pretty sad. I
like that one.
Damn.
I hope it's a sad ending. And I think it
is a sad ending. Yeah, it was a sad
ending. That was kind of a banger. Yeah,
Summer Wars. I don't watch Summer Wars,
but I think that was the director for um
what was it? our our game for the
Digimon movie. That was really good.
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
So, so good.
Girl who left through time felt dumb.
The premise was pretty cool. I liked
how, you know, you you jump and, you
know, jump through time, like the higher
you jump, the further you go back kind
of thing. I Yeah, I I liked it. It's
like a little slice of life, but with a
bit of a, you know, fantasy element to
it. I like one of those um time travel
concepts where
um
there's like a certain limit to it,
like everything must come to an end kind
of thing.
I I I like those.
Yeah.
Oh, race was good. Yeah.
Cosmic Princess Kaguya. Isn't that the
recent one? I don't know about that one.
Um cuz I didn't watch it. I like
Princess Kaguya, the Giblly movie. That
was really good.
Yeah, I was watching with Sally and I
knew how that story was going to end
because I already knew what the story
was going to be about cuz I played I
played Okami.
Yeah,
man. Okami was so good. And they're
going to have Okami, too. So exciting.
Playing Okami. I play Okami Den. And
then there's going to be Okami, too.
Best thing ever.
Yeah. Ah,
these are so nostalgic.
Oh, there's the Ente movie. The Celabe
movie. H Pokemon movies were so good
back. Oh, Mewtwo. Oh, heck yeah. And
then Pokemon the Origin.
That one was a bit more new. I thought
it was still pretty good.
The Lugia one. I probably watch the
Lugia one, too. Yeah,
Pokemon movies were so good back then.
Huh?
Thank you, Toshi.
Yeah,
look at all these. So nostalgic.
And there's a new Yasha movie.
I don't remember anything. Oh,
the art style was really good for the
movie.
They put a lot of effort into it. I I
like that.
for the Inashu movies. You can tell that
they put so much effort
cuz damn.
Oh, damn. It was just different. The
animation was just different. It wasn't
just like anime. Oh, just just anime but
movie. Awesome. No, they put effort into
it. Super. It was so much higher
quality. I h look at the screenshots and
it's really good.
Look at the highlights in those eyes.
Damn.
usually go hard in anime movies.
Um,
yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, they they do. Yeah.
Yeah. I uh Yeah.
Uh
the the line art is nice.
Uhhuh.
Ah, I'm looking at the the first movie
of Inasha. Wait, no. No, it wasn't this
one. The the one that had good art. Oh,
well, they both had good art, but I
think it was two.
That was really nice.
Yeah, two was so nice. Look at the
lighting on that stuff. That's amazing.
Look at the Look at the head highlights.
Oh my god.
They're putting so much effort.
Damn. Look at that. Yeah, look at the
shadows on the thing.
Damn.
Yeah, the art style for this was just
different.
Yeah, it was it was different compared
to the normal anime episodes. Yeah, this
hit.
Damn, this hit.
I need to watch this again now. I I got
to watch it. I got to watch it this
week.
Yeah. I don't know what they did with
two, but the their budget their entire
budget went into movie number two.
Oh yeah. Um I heard that there was a a
new Yasha
anime. Yashaime was it.
I think it's fine if you like that. So,
I just have to say that it's technically
not really canon because
uh
the original creator was only involved
with the character design and nothing
else. So,
that's all I'm going to say.
But there is a new anime that's coming
out. uh done by the same creator
and I think it was called
hold on.
Let me seeashi.
Yeah. Mau.
Yeah. And this looked really cool. It
already came out. What the heck? Why did
nobody talk about it?
What the heck? I didn't even see this on
Twitter. I only saw it on Instagram.
It came out this year. No, it didn't
came out in 2019. It came out this year.
Why did nobody talk about it?
usually.
Oh, hello.
Yeah, but usually when
something pops off, they talk about it.
I I see it usually.
I've never heard of it either.
Well, it's if you liked Inuasha, you
would you might like it. It's uh
you you'll see why.
Yeah. It's like if you liked Rave
Master, you might like Fairy Tale.
Now, did I watch Fairy Tale? No. But,
you know, if you liked it and want to
see more of it, Yeah. go watch it.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
God, but Rave Master Rave Master is so
good, too. Oh, well, I would love to
read this again if I had the time.
Damn.
Yeah, I could probably spend two weeks
just doing nothing but read this.
A new show by the Full Metal Alissus
manga could start airing too. Really?
What's it called?
My web tune backlog. Oh, I'm still
reading it. Don't worry. I I'm catching
up.
Oh wow,
this looks high budget too.
Oh that is cool.
Wow.
Damn.
Anime.
>> Yeah.
Anime. Anime was a good time.
I think the last one,
not anime, but a show that I watched,
uh, that was called Battle of the Fates.
It was because
it was like Sally really recommended it
to me. My family was like, "It's so
good. You should check it out." I was
like, "Sure." I thought it was
interesting. It was like learning about
like a new uh culture in a way. Like not
I wouldn't say self culture. It's just
more like a like a different different
world kind of thing.
Yeah,
that was pretty interesting. The
subtitles were all over the place and it
was a bit frustrating, but it was still
interesting nonetheless.
Is it a Kdrama? No, it's like a reality
like competition.
People are competing as to who can um
do the fortuneelling better basically.
and they kind of predict who,
you know, like maybe find out the reason
as to why or how someone passed away.
And it's Yeah, it's like shamanism.
Yeah, it's it's shamanism.
I thought that was interesting. But
there are so many different types of
people. There are obviously shamans.
There are um tarot card readers.
There are uh what was it?
People who read feet. I guess
a lot of different types of people.
Yeah.
Yeah. There are feet readers.
It was interesting cuz everyone's uh
everyone's heard of reading, you know,
pal. Everyone knows palm reading
footnotes.
Yeah. No, but it's uh new.
Yeah. So it's like, oh that's really
interesting. It's like a different
different world out there. Like how
shamans deal with the spiritual realm is
interesting and different. Anyway, it
was it was an interesting premise. I I
liked it. Would I watch it if there's
season two? I don't know.
Would I watch it again
if someone else would watch it with me?
Sure, why not?
But as for shows, that's
that's all I've watched so far.
Yeah. Nowadays, all I watch are on like
YouTube. I watch uh game reviews.
video video game reviews and
usually like video game summaries.
I watched a bit of Culinary Wars. That
was cool. I didn't finish reading it. I
reading I didn't finish watching it.
I don't have time to watch shows. Yeah,
me too. That's why it's kind of
difficult.
I don't watch let's plays nowadays cuz I
don't have time. Um,
I do watch something that's like, oh,
here's like a a story explanation for
video games or a video game
analysis.
Yeah.
And those are cool.
Or
horror documentaries.
Yeah. But most of them are just video
game analysis and video game summaries.
Lore videos. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Lore videos. Those are good.
Did you do it for Silk Song yet? No.
Even if they did, um I would probably be
avoiding it
cuz they released like videos for let's
say oh Pragmata. I skipped that
cuz I plan on finishing it.
Yeah. Uh, some some of the games that I
want to play, I skip them.
But everything else, I I would watch it
cuz it's free game. Free game. Free real
estate.
Oh yeah. Literally, it's free game.
Like game, but Oh, it's actually game.
Haha, I did not mean to. I'm so clever.
Yeah. Remember how I always told you
guys that
I used to love watching let's players?
Nowadays, all I'm watching are
mysteries, horror,
fidget games
and
looking at my feed.
Interesting.
Japan cleaner goes viral with spa-like
service for soft toys.
No, I shouldn't. No, I shouldn't. I
shouldn't watch this.
Keyboard keyboard stuff
memes.
Interesting. Fidget games, teasers,
cats.
Nice. Okay. Yeah. So, those are
those are what I have.
I've been looking into makeup stuff,
too, again, just to make sure that I'm
still in the game.
And also because I have to
go out and put on makeup cuz it's been a
long time since I uh didn't put on
makeup. So I got to make sure that when
I put on makeup eventually I got to get
back into the game.
Do you look at skin care too? Yeah,
sometimes. Yeah.
going back to Japan in a bit. I mean
also going to
serendipity,
you know. So
yeah.
Oh, how serendipittors.
Yes.
Are you looking forward to the concert
or is it more stress? I I'm looking
forward to it. I'm I'm excited.
I'm not excited about the entire
procedure. I hope they can let me
through without any hassle.
Yeah.
Don't forget your passport again. When
When did I forget my passport?
I only forgot my passport.
No, I didn't forget it. I lost it. That
was in Japan.
Not multiple times. It was just that one
time.
I didn't lo I don't lose it twice. I
lost it just once.
No. No. No. I only lost it once.
That was pretty awful cuz I had to
I had to go so far
as in I had to go back to around the
airport to be able to pick it up. But
hey, the fact that I
got my passport to begin with, that was
a miracle cuz I thought I lost it. But
fortunately, Japan's a very wonderful
place where they don't steal passports.
So
that's nice.
And also, if I lost it, that would have
made things really difficult cuz I had
to go somewhere afterwards, I think.
Maybe for a concert.
Yeah.
Don't lose it in LA. It's okay. I won't
lose it. No, no, no.
I didn't lose I didn't lose my passport
afterwards.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Don't lose your phone. I only lost my
phone.
I lost my phone quite a few number of
times, but hey,
doesn't doesn't everyone
But when I was with the other girls,
I've only lost it once,
and that was when I was hanging out with
Iris. But otherwise, I was good.
Iris took it. Iris took my phone. When
was that? This here.
>> I think something like that happened.
Yeah.
What's she taking?
She actually really wants to have
Android. That's it. She wants a pixel so
bad.
She should just say so.
She thought it was her phone. How? Okay.
Well, I mean, to be fair, all phones,
they look exactly the same. It's just a
It's just a rectangle, a black
rectangle.
And
yeah, I guess it looks different if you
flip it over, but who's going to flip it
over, man?
Yeah,
I wish that we can move on from this
rectangle and just have something new. I
don't know. Maybe the screen can be more
colorful.
Maybe technology will develop better.
And so while it's turned off, it can be
iridescent or something like that. But
then when you turn it on, it's just like
a normal phone.
>> Yeah. Wouldn't that be cool?
Get a handphone like a robot.
No,
they tried it with the glasses thing and
it backfired. Well, I don't want a
glasses thing. I want like a phone, but
something more unique. like instead of
it just being a black screen, I want I
want it so that while it's turned off,
it could be a different color.
Then people would be able to tell that
it's my phone.
Also, it'd be easier to see and it
wouldn't blend in with the environment.
Yeah.
Like, wouldn't that be nice?
A phone that can change colors. Yeah.
Especially the front screen cuz like the
back. Yeah, sure. You can customize it
or whatever. Like you already have other
colors.
But while while it's off, maybe
maybe like the screen can be like
colored differently. Maybe tinted. I
don't know.
But like when you turn it on, it's just
a normal screen. But when you turn it
off,
it's a different color. Like
maybe you can set it or you can decide
which color.
It's not like a screen saver or
anything. Just uh just a see-through
glass. Well, not glass, but like a
see-through material.
like you you can see the bottom of the
screen.
Except not really. You can't. But it
would be really cool if you could see
the bottom of the screen. But it's like
like
you know what I mean?
You know what I'm talking about? Like
instead of a black screen when it's
turned off, it can be
like a red protective cover underneath
this phone screen like underneath it.
And it's like transparent so that it's
see-through
like glass.
Like I get the concept, not the
execution. I mean, I don't get the
execution either. If I knew the
execution, I wouldn't be a VTuber. I
would be an engineer and I'd be making
billions and billions of dollars.
Yeah.
So you can lose it more easily. No, so
that you can distinguish it with other
people.
Yeah.
>> So, so you could you could customize it.
Like for example, let's say your
protective cover is uh blue. Then the
front of your screen when it's turned
off, there's like, you know, there's
this phone screen, right? But the phone
screen is actually uh see-through like
glass. So, you put
like a blue cover, like maybe slide in a
blue cover um underneath the phone
screen. So, when it's turned off, it's
just blue. And then when you turn it
off, I I mean, when you turn it on, it's
a normal screen, but when you turn it
off, it's blue.
And then maybe when it gets more, I
don't know, innovative or something, you
can slide it in with visuals on it.
But why underneath the screen? So that
you know, you can see the color
while it's still off.
It like literal glass. Like literal
glass. Then you can also customize the
front of your screen while it's still
turned off. And also it would make it
stand out amongst all the other phones,
making it easier to find. And also
knowing that it's your phone and not
like thousands and thousands of other
people's phones cuz it's the same black
rectangle. But what if it didn't have to
be like that? What if it can be more
colorful?
Yeah,
a full glass phone.
Yeah, sure. Why not? A full glass phone.
Yeah, sure.
But like a one-way mirror so that people
wouldn't be able to see your screen.
Yeah. Yeah.
Hey, don't you think I'm on to
something? Hey.
Hey, my brain is so big right now.
Might have to move on and pitch it to
some big companies.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Better patent it. Yes.
No. No. It's It's my idea. This This
came all from me. My brilliant head.
If you make it big, we make it big.
Okay. So, now it's only a wee because
you know it's a billion dollar idea. I
see how it is. When it's a bad idea,
you'll just say, "Oh, it's your idea."
But when it's an actually good idea or
say, "Oh, yeah, it's it's our idea."
That's not true.
No, this is my idea.
This is my idea. This is my idea.
Uh-uh.
Oh. Oh, now it's a team. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
So, I don't even know where to begin.
Oh, rage bait segment. Rage bait segment
has been over for so actually it's been
it's been ongoing. Yeah, this entire
conversation
has rage bait moments so I guess it
works.
Yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah.
What's like a good rage bait? Honestly,
it's so easy to rage bait
if you put your mind to it.
But it's just got to happen naturally.
You can't really force it to happen.
Mhm.
Change just chatting to rage bait.
Hey, that's that's a good idea. Hey,
it's my idea now. You're right. I'm
going to I'm going to change the just
chatting streams to just rage bait.
Just be confidently wrong. Ooh.
Yeah,
I do that sometimes and people sometimes
people can't catch on that I'm being
sarcastic. Probably because of the way I
talk, I guess.
But
but for quite a few number of people who
know that it's sarcasm.
Hey,
you know,
I think I think that's British humor.
Yeah.
And where where did we get that humor
from? Obviously
from the U of K.
That's why we have so much in common.
And that's why our spelling is all over
the place.
Like C E N T E R C E N T R E.
The E
drives me crazy.
Yeah. and how it always autocorrects me
when I write something like C O L O R.
Yeah, I remember
getting getting my score deducted from
my essays because I
I wrote them
in American style and not Canadian.
And nowadays
when I look at it, it just looks wrong
without the extra U or like the R and E
switched around.
Sorry, E and R switched around. What am
I saying?
It just doesn't make sense.
Yeah, this is beautiful.
Yeah. You know what they would do? They
would give me a 0.5. They wouldn't They
wouldn't say wrong entirely. They would
just give me a.5
color and color.
That's rough. Yeah, it's okay.
or gray and gray.
Yeah, I still don't know if it's ey or a
y.
I don't know.
Oh, I was really surprised that Duo Tang
was a Canadian thing
cuz growing up Duo Tang was just
I mean that was that was the norm.
Was that
You don't know what a duo tang is?
That's crazy.
a duo tang. Yeah, it's a it's a folder.
Uh we would have it in different colors,
but they're made out of paper usually
like a paper cover
and you can get them in different colors
and then you can label it and uh you put
the loose leaf papers in them.
Yeah.
And then it it has this like little
clip. Uh and so you got to like um put
them either to the side or like uh pull
apart like both pins so that you can
secure the papers in place.
This is just a folder with extra steps.
Yeah, I guess. But it was cool because
we got to have it in different colors
and in a way they were more efficient.
Does it have a zipper? No, just like a
little clip. They they got like three
clips.
Yeah, but folders are probably heavier
is the thing. This one was like um more
lightweight.
I looked it up. It's a binder. It's a
little different from a binder.
Like the the purpose is the same thing,
yes, but it's a lot lighter.
There's a lighter folder, too. Yeah,
sure. But this one was better.
Oh my god, look at this.
Oh, duo tanks.
They did rip like they rip pretty
easily. I hated that.
But it was so nice because
when you would
like have a new year, right, you
switched to a new duo tank, moving on
from all the rip stuff and that was that
was really satisfying.
Yeah,
it couldn't hold that many papers
though. That's okay
because by the time that happened, you
would be moving on to a new year.
Did you have a hole puncher? Yeah, we
did. Oh my god,
that's so nostalgic.
Did you switch schools a lot?
Um,
I switched
Hold on.
I'm trying to keep count.
I
I moved
moved that time
and then I moved again.
Done.
Um.
cannot brain right now. Let me write it
down.
this.
Okay.
Ah, okay.
So,
in
in elementary school, I moved a lot.
I moved five times.
Five elementaryaries.
That's you movie.
Must have been hard making friends. Uh,
yeah, I guess so.
Yeah. I mean,
I guess
Yeah. I mean, I don't know what the
normal is. What? I don't know what the
norm is. Uh I'm assuming that people
that you were friends with in elementary
would move on
uh or at least some of them to another
middle school, I guess.
But I wouldn't know how that's like.
Usually you grow up knowing your
friends. Oh
yeah. For me it was just uh new every
single time.
>> Do you miss your old classmates?
What's there to miss?
I uh yeah I never really got close to um
most of them. I guess there were maybe
few.
There is like one childhood friend that
I was really close with but that was
that was preschool
preschool to grade grade two I guess.
But that was before I moved.
Mhm.
I didn't have middle school. Just
straight to high school. Oh, so
secondary school.
Are you still in contact with a
childhood friend? No, not at all. Cuz I
mean that was preschool. How would I
know?
Yeah.
>> Do you remember their name at least?
Yeah, I do. I still remember their
birthday and their username.
Their username was really easy to
memorize because it was their initials
and their birthday.
Yeah. And we would play video games.
Yeah. Those were good times.
That's a really good memory. Oh,
I guess
I do recognize some people
um
yeah, I do recognize some people um from
elementary when I bump into people. um
even now
and I think to myself, oh yeah, that
person. And it's kind of scary because I
still remember their names. Some of them
I remember their full name,
but I've only met one from my secondary
school and one from
my elementary school.
Yeah.
I'm I'm pretty good with remembering
names.
Yeah,
but with numbers like people's
birthdays. Absolutely no idea.
Yeah,
recently.
Oh, it's hard to say. Recently, I bumped
into someone that I knew uh from my
secondary.
Uh it's been a while.
Yeah.
and she she was she was going to hot
yoga.
I was like, "Oh, yeah. Hey, I remember
you." And I just kind of struck up a
conversation like, "Oh, how have you
been doing?" "Oh, that's awesome. Good
to see you. Small world. Haha.
See you around." And that was it.
It's just like your web tunes maybe,
except more insignificant.
Wow, so extroverted of you. Yeah,
because why not? I mean, it's not really
going to be someone that I'm going to
talk to really, so
why not?
Yeah.
And she was uh doing hot yoga with her
mom. And I also was doing hot yoga with
my mom. And then later on I
remembered her mom's face. So sometimes
when I went to hot yoga I would see her
mom. I wouldn't say hi obviously, but I
just be like, "Oh, she's in the same
class." kind of thing.
Did your mom's talk? Why? No.
If it was like a high school, sure. But
it's like why now?
Huh? Neat. Now let's never speak of this
again. Yeah, I guess. I was just like,
oh, do you have Instagram? Yeah, let's
add each other. Cool. Okay,
well, good luck.
That was it.
They never added each other. We did
actually.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Cuz why not? I don't even use Instagram.
I mean, I I do, but I don't upload
anything. It's basically dead.
I just use it to like send reals to some
of my family members and that's it.
Okay. Now you DM her and be like, "Are
you going to yoga this week?" Easy
friends.
Uh,
no. I'm good.
I'm okay.
I I'm not really dying to make friends
right now.
Um
Yeah, I like my little space.
Yeah,
there's there's no time to make friends.
I mean, yeah, actually, cuz like that
means I have to go outside and I don't
want to go outside.
I only want to go outside when it's
necessary.
Like, if I have too much outside time, I
get I mean, it's a good time. I I have a
good time. Yeah. I don't think about
going home, but
sometimes when there's work, I just
think to myself, damn, I could be
working right now. And then that way I
don't have to worry about things when
I'm outside.
>> Being on your own time is liberating. It
is. I like that.
Yeah. And also,
if I have people to see it, new people
especially, that means I got to put on
makeup. And that's going to that's going
to be a bit of a hassle to take off my
makeup, too.
Just just a hassle all around.
And it's going to ruin my skin. Okay.
Yeah,
that does sound troublesome, right?
she'll be professional when there's an
apocalypse event. I'll be so snatched.
I'm I'm like saving up my skin for when
it's necessary, like seeing people.
Otherwise, I'm just going to go out as
is.
Let Let my face be free.
How does one save up for their skin? So,
you take care of your skin. do this like
daily skin care routine and then maybe
ruin your skin for a little bit when you
go out to see people
yeah
zombies. Oh god, we can't eat them.
They're too snatched.
So on fleek her
she's oramaxing
she's serving h buzz words I can't can't
do anything with Hi.
So that's why. Yep. I mean, I do like
putting on makeup when I actually have
to sit down and do it, but
uh that's that's only when I know that I
have to put it on.
And now there will be some people
saying, "Oh, you can just not put it on
then." No, it's like when you're seeing
people, it's a bit,
how should I say,
uh,
nice. It's like a bit of a
confidence boost and it leaves a good
impression.
Yeah.
Common courtesy. Well, I wouldn't say
common courtesy, but I guess it's just
more like more focused on leaving a good
impression.
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
You have to put on your people friendly
costume. Exactly.
That's why, you know, when I put on
makeup and I go outside, people think
I'm like,
they they think I'm the type of person
who, you know, goes outside, being a
normal person, probably uses Instagram
and uploads them like #blast,
uh, some motivational quote, blah blah
blah. like uh
2026 is serving sparkle emoji. I don't
know, something like that. An extrovert.
Maybe an extrovert would be a a better
way to put it, I suppose. But in
reality, I just want to be home playing
video games.
I just
I just want to be home.
They think you're an Instagram girl.
Well, maybe not to that point, but more
like uh someone who goes outside, maybe.
>> Yeah, it's it's actually pretty funny
because growing up, I've always been
told that
I seem hard to approach,
but that's not true.
Uh, also growing up, I've this is pretty
funny. When I was in elementary, uh, the
adults would ask me if I'm in middle
school. I'm in middle school. They ask
me if I'm in high school. I'm in high
school. They ask me if I'm married.
And And now
they think I'm younger.
They think I'm younger than my age. I'm
I'm regressing. I'm Benjamin Buttoning
right now.
Hello. Oh,
welcome.
Yeah, but it's kind of crazy.
It's kind of funny.
I looked I looked mature, I guess.
Maybe. Sure.
Yeah.
And now people tell me, "Oh, you look
you look younger than I expected." I
say, "What does that mean?" Thank you.
Thank you. Oh my gosh.
Standard aging for Oh, quick age to the
early 20s and stop. Standard aging
pattern for immortals. Immers.
Yes.
You don't look a day over 20.
Ah, you flatter me. Thank you.
Yeah. It's a It's a very big compliment.
Yes.
They tell me that I look like I'm in my
early 20s and I go
and they apologizing. Oh, I'm sorry. I
thought you were I thought you were
really young.
I thought you were still in school. And
I say
oh stop it you
flatter me. H keep it going.
Yeah, but it's it's nice.
Yeah, that's why you guys should always
take it as a compliment when people ask
you to uh show them your ID.
because I always have to show my ID
and then the day that I can't show my
ID, I will be kind of sad.
It gets irritating after a while. Oh, I
didn't know that you went outside so
much. Oh my goodness. Well, you don't
have to tell the world that you're
that you have a life. Stop.
That's for me. That that happens. Uh
um when does it happen?
uh when I have to renew
a card.
Uh so maybe at most once every six
months.
Uh once or twice every 6 months.
So Oh, you must have a life outside.
That's crazy. Wow.
Do you not get groceries?
Why would I need to show them my ID when
I'm buying groceries?
I beg them to check my ID. Oh, that's
that's sad. Oh.
Why are you unsupervised?
Oh, stop.
Keep it going. Stop. What do you mean?
What? You want me to show you my ID or
something? Stop. No.
Shouldn't you be in school right now?
Stop. Oh my god.
Yeah,
you're you're so silly.
Where are your parents? Is this a fake
idea? Stop.
I may not look it, but I'm like
infinite years old.
Yeah, I know. That's pretty crazy. You
think I'm joking, but it's true.
Oh. Oh, you
Yeah.
Yeah,
that's that's nice.
It's it's beautiful. Thank you. Thank
you for feeding my fantasies.
Yeah.
But anyway, moving on. Uh people have
always told me that I
I'm always hard to approach. I've been
told that ever since I was like in grade
eight, maybe.
Let's get you to bed. It's past your
bedtime. This is true. It's uh slowly
getting close to my bedtime, but I still
need to go and record.
Yeah, but that's probably because I
spoke like this since I don't really
know.
I think I started talking like this. Uh,
great
eight.
Yeah,
I think so.
Yeah. So, I think I've been told that
I've been intimidating for a long while
now. Wait, grade eight? Maybe it was
grade nine. I think it was grade nine.
No, it was grade nine. No, no.
Yeah.
Good. Grade grade grade nine sounds
about right.
And then I just kind of stuck with that.
So all or most of high school, I guess.
So
yeah,
it's weird how often confident girls get
told they're intimidating.
The thing is I'm not confident.
Well,
uh,
just just because you don't say anything
doesn't mean that you're intimidating or
confident. Just maybe you're just
introverted.
Yeah, you can LAR confidence. Oh, yeah.
Nowadays I do. Nowadays, I'm really
maybe not really good, but I'm good with
faking confidence. Yeah.
Yeah. People think I'm like extroverted.
Okay. May maybe
extroverted.
Um well, they definitely think I'm like,
you know, that that I have my life put
together.
That's really cool because um like
sometimes sometimes people tell me that
their first impression of me was that
I'm cool and I was like a thank you.
Yay.
Yeah. They they tell me that I seem
really well maybe not really but I seem
cool. I'm like, "Yay!
Oh, I'm acting like a normal person."
Yay.
H wonderful.
Yeah.
And then I I always try to make sure
that I put on a good face, good happy
face. And then I go home, lights off,
uh, lessen as much stimulus as pops as
possible,
and then hopefully not get out of bed
for maybe 3 days.
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Was kind of awesome.
Only 3 days. Yeah. 3 days and then I go
home.
Yeah.
Three days and then go home. Awesome.
When I'm not with my makeup, I uh cannot
be seen without my makeup. That means
I'm not mentally ready. I uh putting on
makeup is basically psyching yourself up
for the big world out there.
And Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
And I think it's kind of nice because
like I I seem passable like a normal
functioning member of society
and maybe I seem like I go out and
socialize a lot more than I do. Like
maybe I seem like the type of person who
uh talks to a lot of people.
Yeah.
Awesome.
That's masking. I'm so good at masking.
Yeah.
But in reality, I'm just really anxious.
I'm really anxious.
I'm laughing. I'm smiling. And I think
to myself, "Oh god.
Oh god."
And then
like sometimes
sometimes I think, oh, uh, I should
probably make eye contact sometimes
because, uh, that creates some time for
more intimacy
and that will that will make the person
feel like they're being listened to. And
also mirroring their actions also help
with feeling more closeness at times.
And
oh, what else?
Yes. And also smile and laugh.
And then be sure to be a listener.
Yes,
blinking is good, too. Blinking is very
good.
Yeah. You know, it's actually really
funny. Um,
yeah, cuz people think I I'm the people
think I'm so good and I'm super conf.
Um, but I had to look up,
well, not I had to, it was just more for
reference, but I read a lot of articles
on how to socialize with people, and I
still have a PDF
um, and I took notes from it
and and it did Help in a way.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I downloaded this back in 2023.
Yeah,
it was uh it's a 200page book. I don't
read all of them, but I tried to read as
much as possible. I think I went up to
maybe I was skimming maybe up to 70
something pages. Uh I was I was looking
at the glossery the the contents and
seeing what would be most beneficial for
me.
Why so recently? Um because I didn't
have
I don't really need to see so many
people. Um
but I had to after
after joining here
then and then then you got to talk to so
many people. So
I I was looking up articles and
um stuff.
Yeah.
And then
and then I was seeing, oh, sometimes you
got to like uh drop their names from
time to time uh because that creates a
bit of closeness. So, I was thinking
that, too.
nowadays it's gotten it's gotten better
because I learned nothing like firsthand
experience but uh yeah but before
it was I mean there's a reason why I
looked it up
yeah but this this book was called how
to win friends and influence
Yeah. And then people were recommending
this um you know like when I was looking
things up like not by other people. I
was just like looking it up and they
said, "Oh, you should check out this
book." So I was like, "Oh, okay." Yeah.
And then I was reading it.
Yeah. It's there are there were some
good takeaways and I still didn't remove
it cuz I figured that it could still be
useful
one day.
Yeah. Yeah. And there's uh uh
like part one fundamental techniques and
handling people. Six ways to make people
like you. And 12 ways to win people to
your way of thinking. Nine ways to
change people without giving offense or
arousing resentment.
And I was I was reading them and I took
notes for things that um that I thought
were useful.
>> All I'm saying you are doing fine before
2023. IMO. Um
well the thing is I was looking up
articles even way before uh Hol live
too. So,
uh yeah.
Yeah.
And then after I joined um
like I was like, "Oh, I should I I
should really um up my skills."
Yeah. And I And I did. And I did and I
got so much better. But again, I got to
put on makeup and everything. Psych
myself up, get ready.
Yeah.
And then and then I'm like burnt out
afterwards cuz uh it's so tiring.
>> Yeah.
I'm proud of you. Thank you. Yay.
>> Yeah, cuz uh when I was younger, um I
didn't I was really shy. Uh the only
reason why I'm you know even before
joining this uh you know even before
joining Hollow Live the reason why I was
still able to uh ask the waiter or
whatever you know ask random people for
directions or whatever was because uh
had to look after I had to look after my
parents and
uh also
Um
like Sally being like like a bigger
sister, like older sister. Uh she was
kind of telling me to do better and kind
of teach me in that way because it's
kind of a hassle if I have to ask
someone else constantly. So I kind of
toughened out
Yeah.
And because I have to help out my
parents and everything else, and if I'm
shy, I can't get things done. So,
yeah,
that's why that's why I do good. I do
well, not good. Well, I do better. I'm
not afraid of asking people.
Yeah. But aside from that, I was still
afraid of talking to people.
Yeah.
Yeah. Because I I don't know. I had so
many bad experiences with people that I
get I I I get kind of cautious.
Would just be anxious being outside, but
it's better. Um,
yeah,
it's better.
That's why I always like being at home
playing my video games
because people are dangerous
and people are dangerous.
>> Yeah.
And now it's like, oh,
you know, people can be kind of cool,
>> but they're still dangerous. They're
still dangerous, but people are cool. So
now I'm a little more open-minded,
but I still also wouldn't mind going
home, but if I'm going to be forced
outside, I might as well try to have a
good time kind of thing. So, you know,
there are still aspects of myself there,
but I'm trying to put myself out there.
Yeah.
So, you're like a cat. I've been told
that a lot. Yeah.
Some people told me that I'm like 100%
cat.
I'm like, "Yeah, I can see that." But
when I was younger, people told me that
I was more like a dog. By people, I mean
Sally. Because uh I was just really
timid is the thing.
Yeah.
I was really timid. I never said I never
really spoke up.
I would just take it as is.
um let things kind of build up uh until
it's at its boiling point and then I
would be really sad.
I mean I was always sad but I would like
hold it in hold in the tears and
everything but then when it's at its
boiling point I would start crying but
like otherwise I would be really timid.
And then there was this um one bad
experience where I that it was like much
later I realized that oh I shouldn't
hold back because uh even though I've
tried all these years to uh be the
better person. I lash out once and I'm
suddenly just as bad as uh you know
this this person. So, I was like, "Oh,
okay. It's so pointless. I should have
just lashed out to begin with, and now I
now I don't really hold back as much."
And uh I guess it's healthier in a way.
>> Yeah.
And and now when I get angry, I just
take a nap.
Yeah. Yeah.
No. When I get annoyed,
I mean, it depends on whether I'm close
to the person, but if I get annoyed, I
show it. I show it. Nowadays, if I'm not
close to the person, I won't show it.
But like if I'm close, I'll show that
I'm annoyed.
It's uh it's normal.
Yeah.
Like you get annoyed with us. I guess
so. Yeah.
Yeah. I used to I used to keep it in all
the time and that was really healthy. Um
it really wasn't that healthy.
Like
yeah it was pretty detrimental. I
suppose
there would be a lot of bad
bad things.
Well, we're the good kind of annoying,
right?
Yeah. Sure. Okay.
Sure, buddy.
Yeah. But it's it's good. It's good now.
It's better.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
You're doing great. Oh, thanks, man.
You're doing great. You're doing great.
Yeah,
it's uh
yeah,
I guess if I were to like talk about
this one incident, um uh there's there's
this
there's this uh
one instance where I
I would like hold back a lot
and
and then I uh you know they're they're
playing their video games and then I
hear them uh talking a mad trash about
me
uh while they're playing their video
games or something and
uh even though I was right there
but I didn't say anything.
Yeah,
they were playing League of Legends.
Yes, they were playing League of
Legends.
Yeah,
it was. But like I didn't even do
anything was the thing. I'm just I'm
just being a little
little timid little thing.
Yeah, I was just I was just going
downstairs to get some water, but yeah.
And they're just like talking mad trash
about me just being like, "Oh, so
annoying." And it's like something over
the stupid thing like, "Oh, oh, it's
because she used the internet
and it slowed down my game."
So damn annoying.
Or like, "Oh, I lost my phone." And then
she wouldn't help me look for it
or something like that.
I don't really know. I don't really
remember what it was, but it was
probably something over like the
smallest things like that.
Yeah.
But like, oh, maybe I didn't want to
look for it because
because the phone is not even in the
house.
Anyway, whatever.
It was It was funny though.
Not really. It kind of sucked.
Yeah.
I was also really good with Smash
Brothers.
Uh yeah, I played Melee, Brawl,
uh Melee and Brawl mostly. And I was I
was pretty good.
And then I would just be playing me
being a very whimsical whimsical soul,
innocent, timid. Let's let's not forget
timid. I was playing Kirby
and then I would just be playing and
then
they get really angry.
They'd be like, "You got to stop using
that specific skill." Like, let's say up
B button or something, I don't know. And
they'd say, "Don't use that because
that's cheating." And then I would have
to
stop using it. And I just say, "Hey, I I
kind of want to quit now." And then
they'd be like, "No."
And then I'd have to keep playing until
until they won.
But I'm also really competitive, so I
don't want to go easy on them either at
the same time.
And then every single time I won, uh,
they leave for a smoke break, just going
like ah. And they'd say really, they'd
say really bad words. They would say the
f word and all sorts of colorful
language and I'd be kind of scared.
And then and then if I let them win then
they would have like kicked up a mad
fuzz.
Yeah, they would probably like flip a
table or something. Who knows? Kick
something. I don't know. But then if I
let them win then they would have been
like I won. And then they get on the
couch or start doing like I don't know
something equivalent to a Fortnite
dance. And I hated seeing that. So, it
was like a lose-lose situation either
way.
Oh my god.
That's why I can't play League.
Actually, I played League only like
halfway into the tutorial and that was
it.
Yeah,
cuz my friend really wanted me to play
League, but I just can't. I just can't
play League. Too many bad memories.
Doesn't help that they also play Dota.
Yeah.
And then
I don't know. Oh, just Oh, so many so
many memories.
Let's talk about the happy memories.
Happy memories.
Yeah,
honestly, when I was younger, I didn't
have a lot of good memories.
But then I do remember some good
memories. Like when I was out fishing,
that was wonderful.
And then I was out digging for clams.
Even though everything else was
horrible, spending time with family was
the best part.
And that was fishing.
And that was digging for clams. And then
more fishing.
And then we get to eat
those fish. And it was gigantic. And we
would catch like eels and they'd be
huge. It would be awesome.
Yeah.
And then it would snow so much so I
would just go and dig out a den for
myself.
That was nice.
Carving out a little den. and thinking,
"Oh, cuz I didn't have a room. I didn't
have my own room."
So, I was thinking, "Oh, if I if I build
if I carve out a little den, then this
could be my room. This is awesome."
Yeah.
And then I would like keep digging until
it's like getting really dark.
Yeah,
that was a really good time. Then I'd be
sometimes I wouldn't have a glove on
like a pair of gloves because uh can't
dig properly.
I was just so obsessed with having a
little little place
was a good time. And then we go
sledding.
Ah, beautiful.
And then
um one of my parents' friends would have
like a little sled track and we would go
sledding
and then crash. It would hurt a lot
because the snow's not even soft. It's
like snow that's frozen over into ice
and it hurt a lot.
Oh, it was pretty bad.
Ah,
I hated that place.
But there were some good memories. But I
also hated that place. My entire family
hated that place. We hated living there.
Worst place ever. Worst people ever.
Worst everything ever. That That was a
character development dark.
I hated that place.
Damn.
Yeah.
At least there were some good memories.
Yeah, I had I had some good memories
there. It was uh it was one of the worst
uh worst places on earth, but also had
one of the better memories
like fishing and clamming. Yeah.
Yeah, that was great.
And moving out
in a car had to travel all the way. um
for such a long time because we couldn't
afford the plane ticket. So, we would
just be on a forced road trip and if we
didn't make it, that could have been
really bad. We shoved everything into
the car.
Then we went on a force road trip
and I had half a seat. I had to do that
for like a week or something. I don't
know.
But that was beautiful. Those road
trips,
those are all memories.
Yeah.
Slept in the car. Yeah. Slept in the
car. Yeah.
Yeah.
had to
had to go to the
the well okay I can't say that but like
went really far went really really far
went from one end to the other
other side of the world
in a car
Yeah. But hardship makes good memories.
Yeah.
And then I remember being like, "Oh my
god, we're here."
Because like we landed in a new
province, right? And then an hour later
it's like, "Oh, we're leaving now."
Maybe not an hour, maybe like 4 hours. I
don't really know. Uh time didn't really
mean anything back then
that we were just relying on a map.
Yeah, cuz it was like, "Oh, welcome."
And then this province, I was like, "Oh,
wow. We're here." It's like, "Farewell."
I was like, "Oh, we're leaving." Well,
this is my first time here and my last
time here, I guess.
Oh,
I get to see the prairies. Oh, no, it's
not a prairie.
Oh, it's this.
Yeah.
Beautiful, beautiful times.
Yeah, th those are good memories. Road
trips. It may be a big hassle, but then
and it is a big hassle, but you look
back on it and you think, you know what,
that was nice spending time with the
family.
The reason why our family is so tightly
knit in a way, I have to be thankful
because it's because that place was so
freaking terrible.
so
so so
bad that we bonded we bonded over
fishing and clamming.
Yeah,
the trauma bonding. Yeah, actually.
Yeah, cuz it was just so bad
and we only had each other
and that was and that's why we're still
tight. It's because of those hardships
that we're still really close. And it's
always family first
and nothing else even now.
Yeah.
Yay.
So there there are pros and cons to
everything, I guess.
Did you encounter hostile wildlife? Yes.
Society
cuz humans can be really freaking
terrible.
Yeah.
But it can also be good.
I thought, you know, back then I
thought,
damn, I hate people so much. I can't
take it anymore. I hate people so much
that my body can't contain itself. I
hate the fact that I'm living in
society. I hate the fact that I'm human.
And even now, sometimes I still feel
like that. However, I think there are
some pros and cons. The fact that I can
play the devil's advocate shows that
I've grown as a person. Wow.
Yeah.
Otherwise, I was thinking, damn, how do
I how do I get a job where I don't have
to interact with anyone? And I was
trying to um find many different ways,
some of them not so good. Uh maybe not
so lethal, but like um otherwise
yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Or maybe like an office work or
something.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
But like now it's good.
Yeah.
A street pharmacist.
Yeah,
but you know, it's like it's it's it's
good now. It's good.
Yeah.
But but now I am surrounded by people
and I'm so anxious but at the same time
it's it's good.
And I really didn't get to travel that
much in my life. So I thought, "Oh, it'd
be really nice if I got to travel." And
now I travel so much that I want to stay
home for like a year straight.
Yay. Wow.
That's why it's a self-fulfilling
prophecy.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Aha.
There's always a silver lining. Yeah.
even though it might take forever to get
there. So that's why if I were to spin
this in an inspirational way, guys,
even even though it feels like maybe
there are times where you feel like
you're just not in a good place, that's
because it's true. You are not in a good
place.
But you will be okay one day, or at
least it'll get better eventually. just
just as long as you keep at it,
right?
Because I was miserable for such a long
time.
And I mean there are still ups and downs
because you know I mean what can you do
really? But it's just that it's better
than before
because back then I was waking up to a
nightmare.
I hated it. I hated being awake. Being
asleep was the best thing ever aside
from playing games.
Yeah.
Yeah. I hated waking up.
I just woke up thinking, "Oh, it's just
every day sucks anyway. Today's going to
suck. Tomorrow is going to suck. This
going to be my life for how long? It's
going to be the same thing.
And I'm never going to be happy
or have a life of my own.
Why do I bother? But see, it's okay.
It's okay. But it took me a long while
to get here.
Yeah.
Just so long as you keep trying, it's
okay.
Yeah,
you need to do a TED talk now. Never.
Because that means I have to stand in
front of so many people and I stumble
over my words and if I make a mistake,
I'm going to kill myself.
Yeah.
Yay.
Yay. You see it?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I I thought I was cooked, guys. I
thought my life was cooked.
Yeah. Genuinely, I thought my life was
cooked.
Yeah, but but now it's okay. Yay.
There are still ups and downs, but it's
it's okay.
Yay. Yay. But you ended up cooking. Oh,
that's so that's so inspirational.
What's the takeaway again? It will get
better eventually.
But then if it's bad now, don't try to
pretend like it's good because it's not
good. And that's toxic positivity.
You got to admit that when things are
bad, things are bad.
And when you can't spin it into
something positive, that's because it's
not positive. But the thing is when
there's a dead end, there's no dead end
because when you hit rock bottom, there
are two reactions like there's no other
way out.
And then the other option which I took
was like, wow,
this is really bad.
Um,
well, like
really can't be it. Like if if this is
it, like what's it going to be?
I was just more curious cuz I'm like,
well, I've hit rock bottom.
What am I
like I mean, what else am I going to do?
Like there's there's nothing else to do
here. And you actually get kind of
creative in a way cuz when you feel like
you're in a dead end, you you find some
sort of way cuz it's like, wow, this is
you actually get kind of impressed for
me. I was really impressed. Um
is is kind of dissociating in a way cuz
I was like, "Wow, this is this is really
bad."
See See guys, when it gets really bad,
you you don't like Yeah. you're like
really sad, but then for me I like, you
know, I crash out, right? And then I I'd
stop and think, "Oh, wow. Wait. Oh, this
is kind of concerning. This is really
bad. That's kind of crazy."
Yeah.
But then you kind of like self-reflect
for a bit cuz it's so bad.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
And then and then you say you do
something about it
cuz it's like well
maybe I guess maybe it's a survival
instinct. I don't know. It's like wow.
I think I think the best way to put is
like you you stop and self-reflect like
wow this is so bad.
It's so bad.
What do I do?
Yeah.
And then and then you get out a little
bit
and then you get dragged down
and then you go back in and then you
struggle on the edge for God knows how
long. Then you crash.
You think, "Damn, it's over." But then,
no. And then you start self-reflecting
for a bit cuz it's like, "Damn, really
is that bad." And then you just like
struggle, go into a little edge and then
then you'll get back out eventually.
Maybe you'll get pushed into it again.
Who knows?
But you got to take your wins.
Yeah.
>> Yeah. I guess it really makes you think.
And by like you, I mean me.
Cuz I'm I'm kind of thinking about it
now. I don't It's not rage bait anymore.
This This is thinking time. This uh
It's that hour.
Yeah. Damn.
I was just thinking over what I said.
I guess I guess that's how I was coping.
It's like, damn, things are really bad.
Then you get kind of shook cuz things
are so bad.
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
Thanks, guys.
So
that helped me realize.
Wow.
Cuz I was I was trying to say something
like, "Oh, well, I've hit rock bottom.
Uh there's no other there there aren't
any options, so might as well climb back
out." It wasn't anything inspirational
like that. It was just more like, wow,
it's so bad.
Kind of scared cuz it's so bad.
Yeah.
Wow.
So, that's how it's been. Ah, that that
makes sense.
Oh, thanks, guys.
Whoa.
Whoa,
that was so
that was so deep.
I'm thinking now. Whoa.
Wow.
Thanks, guys.
Earth.
Whoa. Whoa.
Whoa.
Can we charge you for this session? I
hope it's lowcost counseling. Guys,
speaking of
you, you guys should look into lowcost
counseling. They are very, very useful.
I mean, maybe if there's free
counseling, sure. But then lowcost
counseling. I I I I told you guys before
a lot of the times like counseling can
be expensive, but there's like a uh if
you if you can't quite afford it,
there's like a lower cost counseling.
So, you can just look into that, too.
And also, your insurance could cover for
it, too.
I think I think that's good.
Yeah, there there's an actual lowcost
version. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You should
look into it.
That's pretty It's pretty useful.
Yeah. Usually, let's say like a
counseling could be like $100 an hour,
right? But then if you can't quite do
that, it's uh going to be like lower to
maybe like 20 to $30.
But I think that's a lot more
reasonable. I'm pretty sure
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
You guys should look into it.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I see it.
Oh, no. It's like it's available
anywhere if you look into it. I think
just inquire at your local social
services. Yeah.
And then there you can learn some very
useful strategies, too. It's very good.
They teach you some very useful
techniques. I recommend it, guys.
Yeah, cuz if you feel like you're in a
very bad place or anything, just be sure
to look into it.
Yeah,
I I I think it would be good if you are
going through things
cuz people always say, "Oh, if you're
going through things, uh, be sure to get
professional help." Um, I think I think
that's good.
What if you're in a very mid place? Then
you got to look for someone else.
Yeah.
We should all get group counseling
together. Oh, yeah. It's cheaper that
way, too.
I don't like being vulnerable with a
stranger like that. That's okay, guys,
because they're being paid to do it, so
you feel less guilty about it.
Now, if you were doing that for free, if
someone was doing that to you for free,
you would feel a bit guilty, right? But
like, if they're getting paid to do
that, you feel less guilty or more like,
well, you're getting paid to do it.
Might as well just like tell you
everything.
And it's confidential, too. Yeah. And it
wouldn't be left in your record, so you
don't need to worry about it at all.
Yeah,
they're being paid but not much because
it's low cost. Well, the reason why it's
low cost is for the people who are uh
kind of uh who who can't afford it, but
also those counselors are probably
people who are working to build their
experience.
That would be Yeah. And I think that's
pretty good because that means they get
to have like hands-on experience
um before they like move on to becoming
like professional counselors or
whatever.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Like of course like you know if you're
like complaining to a friend or anything
like you can vent about light-hearted
things but if it's like a more heavy
subject and you do it frequently it's
like they're not really
they're not really there for that.
They're here for good times. I mean bad
times too but like shouldn't be a it
shouldn't lean to one side too much. It
should be balanced. So, if you can't
really do that, you really need someone
to hear you out without feeling like,
oh, you know, I'm overburdening them or
something, you should look into
counseling
and it's it's good and you won't feel
guilty because they're being paid to do
it
and they're also building their work
experience if it's a lowcost counseling.
But what it doesn't change is the fact
that they're still getting paid.
Yeah.
See, uh,
VTubers giving you life experience.
Yeah. And then they get to teach you
great techniques,
a lot of different techniques depending
on what you ask them, like cognitive
behavior therapy.
uh mostly that that's very important but
it's not just that there's also what was
it there's DBT which is also really
useful
yeah
those are very very big
those those techniques once you learn
them they follow you forever ever.
Yes.
Well, that was good. This was very good
conversation.
Is time okay? Time is not okay.
Oh man, I don't want to record.
A
Oh, I don't want to record.
I really don't want to record.
>> And then I had fa today. It was really
good.
I ordered spring rolls
and then salad rolls, but I only
finished uh
[__]
Maybe half a spring roll. That's it.
Okay, maybe not half.
Maybe I had two.
No, not two. Maybe I had the entire
thing. I don't know.
No, maybe it was half
was really good.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
My god. so wonderful. And then maybe
I'll finish everything today and I'll be
so happy.
Tip for the therapist.
I didn't do anything. I was just giving
you some resources.
Do not worry.
I just uh I just think that you know
these types of conversations should be
um should be normal. Well, in like not
normal normal, but in like people
shouldn't be afraid to talk about it
because it's normal that people
uh you know
get help if they need. And
there's this there's this thing too um
which I think is important is that um
like people people usually can come down
with a cold. Uh your body can get sick
and your your mind can get a little sick
too. It can come down with a cold and
when you're sick you go see a doctor and
that's okay. I think that should be
normal. Just like how it is uh when
you're sick coming down with the flu,
you go see a doctor. Should be just like
that.
Yeah, that's just what I think.
Uh-huh.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
All right. Okay. I got to go to sleep
in like an hour and a half.
Are people afraid to go to a doctor in
Canada?
No, they're not afraid.
The government is afraid.
Well, the government's not even afraid.
Nobody's afraid. It's more like
they just don't think about it.
Yeah. Like for example, my my mom, she
has like a really bad shoulder. I have
to like uh go sometime this week. um
with her for like radiology related
stuff. Um but she she has like a really
bad uh shoulder right now. But even
though like X-rays and everything is
like done and everything and shows that
there's some problem, they're not doing
anything about it.
So she's she's like contemplating having
to go out of Canada and get surgery.
So yeah, there it is, guys. If you're
not dying of a, you know,
life-threatening disease,
you know, healthc care, awesome. If you
have a life-threatening sickness, it's
over. Get out. Get out and find
something else. Do not wait. It might be
too late.
This is coming from experiencing other
people who was too late for them. So,
don't don't do it. Don't do it.
If it's not lifethreatening,
stay. If it is lifethreatening,
get out.
Yeah.
Okay. Well, you know what? On that
positive note, I'm going to go now. Hey,
the the take away from that is if if you
need help, don't just sit there. Do
something. If it's really bad, do
something.
Otherwise, it might be too late.
Okay.
Good night,
maybe I'll read the tomorrow. Yeah,
that'd be awesome.
I hope I finish my work, at least most
of them, today. Yay. Yay. Okay.
It was really good talking to everyone.
Oh my god. I feel like it's been a while
since I've spoken this much.
I really don't think I've spoken this
much in a a while.
It was kind of nice. Maybe I talk too
much.
No, I don't talk too much. I do talk a
bit, but it's pretty nice. I
This so it's so fun.
So fun. I get to I talk to people. So
cool. Isn't that wonderful? That's the
magic of the internet. You get to talk
to so many people. You get to be in
touch with so many people while also
being able to just chill out in your own
little space. Isn't that nice? You guys
are probably lying in bed or like I
don't know sitting
working. I don't know. But you're
probably in your own space. That's
really nice. That's wonderful. Isn't the
internet great? has its pros and cons,
but sometimes when it's great, it's so
great.
Okay, I'm done.